<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 05:44:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I was hacked!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hacked/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 05:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hacked/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.jakesaunders.dev/my-server-started-mining-monero-this-morning/&#34;&gt;Jake Saunders wrote&lt;/a&gt; about discovering that a recent Next.js vulnerability allowed hackers access to their server through an Umami instance. I use Umami, too!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I logged into my VPS and didn&amp;rsquo;t see any suspicious files or running processes. I then opened my Umami dashboard to poke around, and my browser immediately opened a window to a gambling site. Well, shit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;damage-assessment&#34;&gt;Damage assessment&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The browser&amp;rsquo;s developer console showed that an &lt;code&gt;onclick&lt;/code&gt; event was added to the &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;html&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; object, and this was originating from a file disguised to look like a standard Next.js library file used by Umami. So the attacker was able to modify and add files, as well as spoof the modified date to hide their tracks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I may have outgrown Coolify</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/outgrowing-coolify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 13:35:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/outgrowing-coolify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I initially chose &lt;a href=&#34;https://coolify.io/&#34;&gt;Coolify&lt;/a&gt; as a self-hosted alternative to Heroku when it got too expensive. Coolify makes a lot of things very easy, but I ended up having to dig in to the details and learn a lot to fix things that didn&amp;rsquo;t work. Now that I have learned a fair bit about server management, I&amp;rsquo;ve found that I may no longer need Coolify&amp;rsquo;s hand-holding.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;venturing-into-self-hosting&#34;&gt;Venturing into self-hosting&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I knew next to nothing about Linux servers, Docker, reverse proxies, and the like. I had used Heroku for a long time, but its base price became restrictively expensive considering how small each of my little projects was, so I started looking for a service that could ease me into self-hosting my apps on a VPS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
