<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fediverse on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/fediverse/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fediverse on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 14:23:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/fediverse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Identity and Community on the Fediverse</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/identity-vs-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 14:23:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/identity-vs-community/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://fediverse.info&#34;&gt;The Fediverse&lt;/a&gt;, a network of interconnected social media services, requires users to choose a service for their account, tying their identity to that community. This can be problematic if the community experiences issues like spam, moderation problems, or shutdown. If we could decouple identity from community, like Reddit did with subreddits, users could more freely participate in multiple communities — and the network overall would be more accessible and resilient.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing GoToSocial on Coolify</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-gotosocial-on-coolify/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-gotosocial-on-coolify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Following up to my &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/2024/12/02/i-want-to-love-mastodon.html&#34;&gt;earlier post about the fediverse&lt;/a&gt;, I discovered &lt;a href=&#34;https://gotosocial.org&#34;&gt;GoToSocial&lt;/a&gt;. Compared to Mastodon which required a fair amount of server overhead (more than I could justify for just playing around online), GoToSocial is very &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.gotosocial.org/en/latest/getting_started/#server-vps&#34;&gt;lightweight&lt;/a&gt;: 1 CPU, 1GB memory, and 15GB-20GB of storage space for the first year or so. Sold!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This would let me set up my own single-user server, which solves all of my misgivings about Mastodon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;callout&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;I am a total novice at all things server-related! I am probably at least a little bit wrong about some of the things I write here. Please take my experience with a grain of salt, and correct me if you can.&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have a VPS with &lt;a href=&#34;https://coolify.io&#34;&gt;Coolify&lt;/a&gt; to manage the multiple apps I have running, and all things considered it makes things very easy.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I used a docker-compose file to deploy GoToSocial, and their &lt;a href=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/superseriousbusiness/gotosocial/main/example/docker-compose/docker-compose.yaml&#34;&gt;example file&lt;/a&gt; was almost perfect as-is.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
