<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robot on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/robot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Robot on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/robot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Detroit: Become Human</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/detroit-become-human/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/detroit-become-human/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/2020/detroit.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;aside&#34;&gt;In this review, I&#39;ll talk about a few parts of the game that stood out to me, and I&#39;ll do my best to do so while avoiding spoilers.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Detroit: Become Human&lt;/em&gt; is a story-heavy adventure game developed by Quantic Dream, the studio I knew best as the creators of &lt;em&gt;Heavy Rain&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The story takes place in a future where androids are commonplace and indistinguishable from humans aside from a computer chip placed on their temple. Predictably, the androids are mistreated and repressed by humans, and you eventually find yourself in the middle of a robot uprising.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Materials Science with Machine Learning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/automating-materials-science-with-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/automating-materials-science-with-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A robot arm dips a pipette into a dish and transfers a tiny amount of bright liquid into one of many receptacles sitting in front of another machine. When all the samples are ready, the second machine tests their optical properties, and the results are fed to a computer that controls the arm. Software analyzes the results of these experiments, formulates a few hypotheses, and then starts the process over again. Humans are barely required.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
