<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Japan on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/japan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Japan on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/japan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Buy local</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/buy-local/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/buy-local/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I look at reviews before buying things, and I prefer personal websites and youtube channels over large publications because I can get a feel for the person behind the opinions, and their preferences. I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed though that reviews gravitate towards a certain subset of good, but mostly American brands. This is only a problem because I live in Japan, where limited availability and terrible exchange rates makes everything feel twice as expensive as they ought to be.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos of Japan that haven&#39;t changed in 150 years</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/old-japan-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:18:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/old-japan-photos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was pointed to an &lt;a href=&#34;https://cosmographia.substack.com/p/photographs-of-old-japan&#34;&gt;article on Cosmographia&lt;/a&gt; which in turn shared &lt;a href=&#34;https://sova.si.edu/record/fsa.a1999.35?s=0&amp;amp;n=10&amp;amp;t=C&amp;amp;q=japan&amp;amp;i=1&#34;&gt;an archive of photos taken in 19th century Japan&lt;/a&gt;. These are amazing photos, but what struck me was how &lt;em&gt;familiar&lt;/em&gt; some of them felt. Photos taken from 150 years ago should feel like looking into another world, but some of these scenes, the architecture, are still very present today. It makes it clear how cultural artifacts are so remarkably well-preserved here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When a music festival was cancelled, idol fans supported the local community</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/momokuro-fans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:44:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/momokuro-fans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some uplifting &lt;a href=&#34;https://news.yahoo.co.jp/articles/f3dc7027f17ec3d90e0da75d8f622e12452f471a&#34;&gt;news from Japan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On April 13th in Shibata City of Niigata prefecture (Japan), the popular idol group &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.momoclo.net&#34;&gt;Momoiro Clover Z&lt;/a&gt; had been planning a large music festival in cooperation with a large number of other artists, as well as local police, schools, and city government. However, on the day of festival the weather took a turn for the worse, and warnings were issued for strong winds, flash floods, and avalanches.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The geometric nests of the white-spotted pufferfish</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-geometric-nests-of-the-white-spotted-pufferfish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:25:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-geometric-nests-of-the-white-spotted-pufferfish/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The white-spotted pufferfish, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://amami-horizon.com/en/nature/ocean/amami-hoshizorafugu&#34;&gt;Amami hoshizora fugu&lt;/a&gt;, is a species of pufferfish newly discovered in 2014 near Japan&amp;rsquo;s Amami-Oshima Island. The males spend roughly a week constructing an elaborate circular nest about 2 meters in diameter to attract females.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Divers had known about these structures that appear in early summer every year, but apparently it took a while to catch the fish in action.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/2025/whitespottedpuffer_nest.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The circular nest of the white-spotted pufferfish&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sorry the Elevator is Crowded</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sorry-the-elevator-is-crowded/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sorry-the-elevator-is-crowded/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The elevator in our office building has a small LCD panel that shows information like the current floor, but when the total weight of passengers crosses a certain threshold it also adds a short note: &amp;ldquo;Sorry the elevator is crowded&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It struck me – of all possible features for an elevator display, how did they decide that they needed this one? It has no impact on the elevator&amp;rsquo;s function of moving people vertically. And a crowded elevator is not the elevator&amp;rsquo;s fault (although this is most likely just an example of Japan&amp;rsquo;s self-deprecating approach to hospitality). So why was this message deemed necessary?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leather Sneakers by Spingle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/leather-sneakers-by-spingle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/leather-sneakers-by-spingle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/spingle.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.spingle.jp/en/&#34;&gt;Spingle&lt;/a&gt; is a company based in Hiroshima, Japan that makes hand-crafted leather shoes, and they also have an excellent &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.spingle.jp/en/spingle_move/&#34;&gt;sneaker lineup&lt;/a&gt;. Because the leather molds to your feet over time, the shoes become more comfortable the more you wear them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They are a little pricey, but they should last a long time and the cost is completely reasonable considering the work that goes into them. And there are plenty of sneakers that cost even more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ōkunoshima - The Island of Bunnies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/okunoshima---the-island-of-bunnies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/okunoshima---the-island-of-bunnies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/okunoshima/okunoshima24.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Located east of Hiroshima in the Seto Inland Sea, Ōkunoshima (大久野島) is a small island home to over 700 rabbits. The rabbits are wild but friendly, and tourists arrive every day with bags full of food and treats. The island was relatively unknown in Japan until recently when its populality among foreign visitors brought it into the spotlight.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- more --&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-dark-history&#34;&gt;A Dark History&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ōkunoshima today is a paradise of cuteness, but its origins are sinister. Chosen for its remote location, it contained secret facilities used to develop and produce poison gas for chemical weapons. The island was erased from maps at the time to hide its existence. The ruins of these facilities still exist, covered by moss and providing a grim backdrop for those who choose to explore the island.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Cut of the Dead (カメラを止めるな！）</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/one-cut-of-the-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/one-cut-of-the-dead/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://kametome.net/index.html&#34;&gt;One Cut of the Dead (カメラを止めるな！)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is a low budget Japanese zombie movie that became hugely popular here. I just watched it over the weekend and it was wonderful. The writing is very funny and very clever, and when it was over I found myself immediately wanting to watch it a second time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/One_Cut_of_the_Dead&#34;&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One Cut of the Dead was made for 3 million Japanese Yen (approximately $25,000 in US Dollars at the time) with a cast of unknown actors. It was made in eight days after director Shinichiro Ueda participated in workshops for actors and filmmakers at the Enbu Seminar drama school in Tokyo&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>夜桜</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/yozakura/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/yozakura/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/yozakura.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/yozakura_s.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;夜桜&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo&#39;s Cityscape Recreated With Stickers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/tokyos-cityscape-recreated-with-stickers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 23:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/tokyos-cityscape-recreated-with-stickers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By artist &lt;a href=&#34;http://yukinoart.wix.com/home#!__news&#34;&gt;Yukino Ohmura&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/tokyo-sticker.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rainbow Bridge&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pray for Japan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pray-for-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pray-for-japan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After the 3/11 earthquake, #prayforjapan was a hashtag used for people around the world to send messages of encouragement to Japan. &lt;a href=&#34;http://prayforjapan.jp/&#34;&gt;prayforjapan.jp&lt;/a&gt; is a site that is collecting heartwarming tweets from Japanese users, as well as messages from outside the country.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I got emotional after reading just a few of these messages. The earthquake was a terrible tragedy, but amidst all of that I feel admiration for the spirit of the Japanese people. Messages like this show that people have really come together to help one another, and it give me great hope for the country’s recovery.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
