<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:39:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>If you love something, pay a subscription fee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pay-a-subscription/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:39:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pay-a-subscription/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a rule of thumb, you are more likely to be satisfied by a service that you pay for directly. This is because paying money makes you a &lt;em&gt;customer&lt;/em&gt; of the business, and the business is thereby directly motivated to keep you satisfied.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you want to find a service that will satisfy you for a long time, &lt;em&gt;paying a subscription&lt;/em&gt; is your best bet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are some facts:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In general, a business aims to please its customers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A business&amp;rsquo;s customers are &lt;em&gt;those who pay it money&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you do not pay money to a business, you are not its customer.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A user of a service who does not pay is, strictly speaking, not a customer. In most cases, the needs of the user and the needs of the customer are not too far apart, so many non-paying users are generally satisfied. But on average, in the long run, the needs of the non-user customer and the needs of the non-customer users will drift apart.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wag Buys Shares Back from SoftBank</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/wag-buys-shares-back-from-softbank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/wag-buys-shares-back-from-softbank/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wag was looking to raise $75 million. It went to SoftBank and was like &amp;ldquo;will you give us $75 million?&amp;rdquo; SoftBank was like &amp;ldquo;no haha we’ll give you $300 million,&amp;rdquo; because that is SoftBank’s whole thing, it loves to give startups vastly more money than they want or need. And so Wag took the money. And then like a year and a half later Wag will get rid of SoftBank by giving back, I don’t know, but I am going to say some number less than $225 million (&amp;ldquo;well below&amp;rdquo; the valuation at which it invested). Wag got the $75 million it needed for free.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Maker&#39;s Schedule - A Ten Year Retrospective</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-makers-schedule-a-ten-year-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-makers-schedule-a-ten-year-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;10 years ago, I was fresh out of college and encountered &lt;a href=&#34;http://paulgraham.com/makersschedule.html&#34;&gt;Paul Graham&amp;rsquo;s essay&lt;/a&gt; about the maker&amp;rsquo;s schedule, and wrote &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/programmers-stop-whining-be-productive&#34;&gt;a response&lt;/a&gt; disagreeing with the spirit of the article. While I knew and understood that programmers could be much more productive in one 10 hour chunk than in five 2 hour chunks, I felt like rearranging a business&amp;rsquo;s operations based on these preferences was going overboard. The typical programmer as described seemed undisciplined, and I wrote that programmers needed to find ways to work around distractions, which are simply a fact of life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Value Promise of Subscription Games</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-value-promise-of-subscription-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-value-promise-of-subscription-games/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had been playing World of Warcraft on and off for about 10 years, but I decided to stop playing again about a year ago. I quit because of a series of changes that were made to the game, and it motivated me to think about why I reacted that way as a paying customer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A series of recent changes made to WoW were designed to motivate players to play by ensuring they always gain something and grow a little every time they play. Unfortunately, a side effect of these changes was an increased pressure to spend many hours playing. This made me feel like my limited time spent in the game was less valuable, and is what ultimately led to me quitting the game.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Value of Blockchain Platforms</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/blockchain-platforms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 21:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/blockchain-platforms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking a lot recently about what benefits there are to building a new product on a blockchain. Blockchains allow an app to be decentralized, and the biggest value they bring is a solid way to handle trust and consensus in an environment with no central authority. I was having a hard time thinking of products that would really benefit from being decentralized, but I came across an idea about decentralized platforms that makes a very strong case for using blockchains.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Steps to an Effective Tech Team</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/five-steps-to-an-effective-tech-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/five-steps-to-an-effective-tech-team/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently experienced two of the most informative and useful meetings of my life. Lloyd Taylor, the former VP of Technical Operations at LinkedIn, and Olana Khan, the former COO of Kiva, graciously donated their time to speak to us about how to organize our technology goals. We had been in the process of formalizing our thoughts for an upcoming board meeting, but their expert feedback allowed us to cement in some much-needed structure. In addition, we also were given invaluable advice about how to lead an effective technology team in general.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook and Non-Profits: Revolutionizing with Samasource</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/facebook-and-non-profits-revolutionizing-with-samasource/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/facebook-and-non-profits-revolutionizing-with-samasource/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Originally posted on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://fbfund.com/facebook-and-non-profits-revolutionizing-with-samasource/&#34;&gt;fbFund blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While a Stanford undergrad, I began my online career with gleeful audacity. The Monday after Facebook Platform launched, my friend and I released Facebook&amp;rsquo;s original Graffiti application. We were unexperienced and had no viral component, so we soon lost the battle to Mark Kantor et al.&amp;rsquo;s version. But Graffiti gave us excitement and hunger. The following fall we enrolled in Stanford&amp;rsquo;s course on Facebook applications, using the opportunity to develop Send Hotness. This time, we nailed the virality. A few advertising payouts later, we were the proud owners of two companies. Doped up on adrenaline, we loved every minute. I stepped down eventually once I remembered that I had schoolwork to do, but I felt sure that this was my path.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programmers: Stop Whining, Be Productive</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/programmers-stop-whining-be-productive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/programmers-stop-whining-be-productive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[!NOTE] Update 2019&#xA;10 years later, I have posted a reflection on this piece [[the-maker&amp;rsquo;s-schedule-a-ten-year-retrospective | here]].&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was pointed to &lt;a href=&#34;http://paulgraham.com/makersschedule.html&#34;&gt;Paul Graham’s post&lt;/a&gt; about programmers running on a separate schedule than other people. Programmers run on the &amp;ldquo;maker’s schedule&amp;rdquo; and prefer to work in large chunks of time, with units of at least half a day. Others, particularly their bosses, operate on the &amp;ldquo;manager’s schedule&amp;rdquo; and have things defined into hour-long chunks. Interactions between the two typically cause friction:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samasource Selected for fbFund REV</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/samasource-selected-for-fbfund-rev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/samasource-selected-for-fbfund-rev/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hooray! Along with 18 companies and one other non-profit, &lt;strong&gt;Samasource was chosen to participate in fbFund’s incubator program this summer&lt;/strong&gt;. Check out the full list of winners on &lt;a href=&#34;http://venturebeat.com/2009/05/28/fbfund-17-companies-and-2-nonprofits-win-head-to-palo-alto/&#34;&gt;VentureBeat&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.insidefacebook.com/2009/05/28/facebook-announces-19-2009-fbfund-winners/&#34;&gt;InsideFacebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What this means is that we’ll have Palo Alto office space, lots of media attention, an official Facebook seal of approval, and possibly free lunches &lt;em&gt;/crossfingers&lt;/em&gt;. The catch?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Due to the way fbFund is structured, the non-profit startups cannot receive funding (&lt;a href=&#34;http://developers.facebook.com/news.php?blog=1&amp;amp;story=249&#34;&gt;Facebook dev blog&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
