<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shape Up - How Basecamp does Product Development</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/shape-up-how-basecamp-does-product-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/shape-up-how-basecamp-does-product-development/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://basecamp.com/shapeup&#34;&gt;Shape Up&lt;/a&gt; is an amazing new web-book by Basecamp that details the process they use to define, build, and ship their products. It has great insights, but I especially appreciated how many of the ideas presented just make a lot of sense. I often nodded along in agreement and recognized concepts that we share in our team. The framework is battle-tested and realistic, and there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to integrate some new ideas into our existing workflow without having to reorganize how we think about everything to fit a new metaphor.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Steps to an Effective Tech Team</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/five-steps-to-an-effective-tech-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/five-steps-to-an-effective-tech-team/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently experienced two of the most informative and useful meetings of my life. Lloyd Taylor, the former VP of Technical Operations at LinkedIn, and Olana Khan, the former COO of Kiva, graciously donated their time to speak to us about how to organize our technology goals. We had been in the process of formalizing our thoughts for an upcoming board meeting, but their expert feedback allowed us to cement in some much-needed structure. In addition, we also were given invaluable advice about how to lead an effective technology team in general.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
