<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Probability on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/probability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Probability on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 15:40:30 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/probability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Time Everyone &#34;Corrected&#34; the World’s Smartest Woman</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/the-time-everyone-corrected-the-worlds-smartest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 15:40:30 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/the-time-everyone-corrected-the-worlds-smartest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;In 1990, Marilyn vos Savant correctly answered a probability puzzle in her column for Parade Magazine. And then, the world called her an idiot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I still remember the chaos caused by the Monty Hall problem in our high school math class. Here&#39;s my explanation for how it works:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your first choice could either be a car or a goat.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;ol&gt;&#xA;    &lt;li&gt;If you picked the car, you will win the car by not changing your guess.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;    &lt;li&gt;If you picked a goat, the host will reveal the second goat. The last door left will be the car, so you are guaranteed to win if you change your guess.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You have two possible strategies to win the car:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;ol&gt;&#xA;    &lt;li&gt;Try to pick the car on your first guess, and don&#39;t change the guess.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;    &lt;li&gt;Try to pick a goat on your first guess, and change the guess after the host opens another door.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The second strategy is better, since picking a goat is twice as easy as picking the car.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The best strategy is to &lt;em&gt;try to pick a goat&lt;/em&gt; in round 1. Once the host has revealed the second goat, you are guaranteed the car by switching doors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
