<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rebranding the site: Invisible Parade</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/rebranding-the-site-invisible-parade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/rebranding-the-site-invisible-parade/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I first started this personal website just about 20 years ago. It began as a couple of html pages, and spent time as a Wordpress blog, a Tumblr page, and is now a static blog generated by Jekyll. Through that time, it had always just had my name, alexonsager.com. This year, I’m rebranding it to &lt;strong&gt;Invisible Parade&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;being-online-then&#34;&gt;Being online then&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I started this site I had just entered university, got my first MacBook, and was excited to become a full-fledged citizen of the internet. At the time, I thought it was cool to publish as much of yourself as possible. Tag yourself and your friends in the photos you take, scrobble the music you listen to, check in to the places you go, tweet your thoughts. Since I was broadcasting myself to the world, it made sense to put my name on my website. That’s how people would know me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procrastination and Fear of Failure</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/procrastination-and-fear-of-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/procrastination-and-fear-of-failure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I tend to procrastinate if I let myself, so I&amp;rsquo;ve tried my share of techniques to keep it in check. At some point, I read that a fear of failure can cause procrastination, and this really resonated with me. Realizing this has helped me understand where my urge to put things off is coming from.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If I have a large task in front of me, my mind rushes through everything that needs to be done and affirms how difficult it will be. I imagine (mostly subconsciously) all the ways that my output will be less than ideal, and that is what keeps me from taking action.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Father&#39;s Bookshelf</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-fathers-bookshelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-fathers-bookshelf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For a long time, I&amp;rsquo;ve avoided collecting too much stuff. I buy Kindle versions of books whenever possible, but there is a small shelf for the few books I have carried around with me over the years. My son, who is not quite two years old, will sometimes rummage through my books and leave them in a heap once he realizes there are no pictures, but it made me remember what my own father&amp;rsquo;s bookshelf was like for me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful vs. Effective Prose</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/beautiful-vs.-effective-prose/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/beautiful-vs.-effective-prose/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A long time ago, I fancied myself a writer and strove to write beautiful prose. I read a lot and borrowed from styles that I admired, but oftentimes my sentences ran on, and I relied on my thesaurus too heavily. But I enjoyed the process of writing and reached a familiarity with words that allowed me to simply let my thoughts flow through my fingers onto the page.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At university, I discovered &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Elements_of_Style&#34;&gt;The Elements of Style&lt;/a&gt; and quickly became an advocate instead of lean, effective prose. I strove to convey my thoughts using fewer words. Composition took more effort as I scrutinized each phrase. I was happy with the results, and I felt a deliberate craftsmanship that seemed more pronounced than before.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ōkunoshima - The Island of Bunnies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/okunoshima---the-island-of-bunnies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/okunoshima---the-island-of-bunnies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/okunoshima/okunoshima24.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Located east of Hiroshima in the Seto Inland Sea, Ōkunoshima (大久野島) is a small island home to over 700 rabbits. The rabbits are wild but friendly, and tourists arrive every day with bags full of food and treats. The island was relatively unknown in Japan until recently when its populality among foreign visitors brought it into the spotlight.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- more --&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-dark-history&#34;&gt;A Dark History&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ōkunoshima today is a paradise of cuteness, but its origins are sinister. Chosen for its remote location, it contained secret facilities used to develop and produce poison gas for chemical weapons. The island was erased from maps at the time to hide its existence. The ruins of these facilities still exist, covered by moss and providing a grim backdrop for those who choose to explore the island.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Lighting in the Office</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/natural-lighting-in-the-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/natural-lighting-in-the-office/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve come to learn that I really enjoy working in environments with only natural lighting. At my job, I work in a large open room with about 50 people. Many of them are artists who need to minimize the glare on their screens, so the great big windows covering the walls of our room are always covered with blinds, and we instead have fluorescent lights turned on (these do cause glare too, but at least they are more predictable so people can tilt their screens to minimize it).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mental Training, and Learning to Swim</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mental-training-and-learning-to-swim/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mental-training-and-learning-to-swim/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;During my last year at university, I decided to learn to swim. I was reasonably confident in my ability to stay afloat in deep water and not die, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t what you could call swimming. Luckily, two of my close friends were excellent swimmers and they agreed to work with me in the mornings before class.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As an aside, I did take swimming lessons on and off for a few years when I was a kid, but apparently I retained nothing from those classes. Maybe I was just a terrible swimmer the entire time? Possibly related, &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/i-grew-up-in-high-school&#34;&gt;I have very few memories from my elementary and middle school years&lt;/a&gt;, so I have a suspicion that I didn&amp;rsquo;t do a whole lot of thinking when I was a kid. In any case, I was essentially a total beginner to swimming when we started. I knew that you kicked your legs and paddled with your arms to go forward, but that was about it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucid Dreaming</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lucid-dreaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lucid-dreaming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was consistently able to have lucid dreams when I was in high school. Partway through a dream, I would realize that I was dreaming and could then control the rest of the dream to a small extent. As I&amp;rsquo;ve grown older though, this has become less and less common. Maybe age has changed something about my brain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Naturally, I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in lucid dreaming and have read a lot about it. &lt;a href=&#34;https://tim.blog/2009/09/21/how-to-lucid-dream/&#34;&gt;Tim Ferriss has a fascinating beginner&amp;rsquo;s guide on his blog&lt;/a&gt;. Different people seem to have different approaches and theories, so I thought I would write about my own experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let’s stop the hate</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lets-stop-the-hate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 18:44:38 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lets-stop-the-hate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m a supporter of LGBT rights. I&#39;m generally not too vocal about it, but with recent events culminating in the Orlando mass shootings, I had to say something.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve been thinking a lot about the LGBT rights movement recently. Hopefully this effort can be another step forward following the Civil Rights Movement, as we work towards equal rights and treatment for all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Civil Rights Act made it illegal to discriminate based on race, color, religion, sex, or national origin. Setting religion aside for a moment, the rest are distinctions that generally lead to noticeable physical differences. The ease of identification is probably one factor that helped the prejudice spread so much, and led to institutional disenfranchisement as well as terrible acts of discrimination and violence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Be Polite</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/how-to-be-polite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2014 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/how-to-be-polite/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most people don’t notice I’m polite, which is sort of the point. I don’t look polite. I am big and droopy and need a haircut. No soul would associate me with watercress sandwiches. Still, every year or so someone takes me aside and says, you actually are weirdly polite, aren’t you? And I always thrill. They noticed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Politeness buys you time. It leaves doors open. I’ve met so many people whom, if I had trusted my first impressions, I would never have wanted to meet again. And yet — many of them are now great friends.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone 5 Wallpaper - Stormtrooper Prism</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/iphone-5-wallpaper-stormtrooper-prism/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 13:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/iphone-5-wallpaper-stormtrooper-prism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/assets/images/stormtrooper.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/stormtrooper_s.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Stormtrooper Prism&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please let me know if you know the source of this image.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;UPDATE: Artwork by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.liambrazier.com/&#34;&gt;Liam Brazier&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminal Theme</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/terminal-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 15:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/terminal-theme/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/terminal.png&#34; alt=&#34;New Terminal setup&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can download the theme &lt;a href=&#34;http://images.alexonsager.net/downloads/Base16.terminal.zip&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Colors were taken from the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/chriskempson/base16-textmate&#34;&gt;Base16 TextMate theme&lt;/a&gt;, and the font is &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/fonts/specimen/Source+Code+Pro&#34;&gt;Source Code Pro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://backup.noiseandheat.com/blog/2011/12/os-x-lion-terminal-colours/&#34;&gt;These&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://osxdaily.com/2013/02/05/improve-terminal-appearance-mac-os-x/&#34;&gt;sites&lt;/a&gt; describe how to get your Terminal to start showing colors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Grew Up in High School</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/i-grew-up-in-high-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/i-grew-up-in-high-school/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I might even say that I didn’t grow up in any meaningful way before I started high school.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve always felt like I have very limited memories of middle school and elementary school. The problem, as I realized recently, isn’t that I have few memories. Rather, it is that my memories don’t seem to include my thoughts – what I wondered, what I thought about, and how I felt about certain things. When probing my memories I get plenty of clear images, but I can’t help but feel like an observer; I can see my past-self doing things and reacting to events, but I have no idea what that child was thinking. I mean, I can guess. I’m sure I’d be pretty good at guessing, since I know the kid well, but it’s strange that this isn’t part of the memory.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a Better Writer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/becoming-a-better-writer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 15:39:05 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/becoming-a-better-writer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I just ordered Strunk &amp;amp; White&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Elements of Style,&amp;rdquo; 50th anniversary edition. I don&amp;rsquo;t have the book yet, but the purchase inspired me to pay more attention to writing. Hopefully this can be someplace where I can practice writing, incorporating new ideas and polishing my prose. No high hopes yet, as I don&amp;rsquo;t often continue such things for long, but we&amp;rsquo;ll see how it goes :)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Movie Watch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/upcoming-movie-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 04:49:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/upcoming-movie-watch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Documentary Type&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.apple.com/trailers/weinstein/whereintheworldisosamabinladen/trailer/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt; Where in the World is Osama Bin Laden?&lt;/a&gt; - Before you write this movie off as one that sounds like it was done by those guys that make stupid teen movies (I almost did), go watch the trailer. It&amp;rsquo;s done by the guy who made Supersize Me, and chronicles his quest to find Osama Bin Laden. And the trailer plays Gogol Bordello music.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.apple.com/trailers/independent/planetbboy/trailer/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Planet B-Boy&lt;/a&gt; - A documentary on the breakdancing culture. This movie looks awesome.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outside of Target</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/outside-of-target/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 17:46:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/outside-of-target/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The other day, a woman asked me if I could spare some change for poor women and children, and my automatic response was to keep walking with no response. Then, as I was walking away she called out to me and said &amp;ldquo;God bless you.&amp;rdquo; Hearing that made me feel like an awful person, because I certainly didn&amp;rsquo;t do anything to deserve it. It was on my mind for a while after that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why vote?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 09:05:16 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-vote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;People say that voting doesn&amp;rsquo;t really matter, because in the big picture, one vote for one candidate isn&amp;rsquo;t really going to make that much difference. And this is something that I&amp;rsquo;ve had a hard time coming to terms with too, but I think I figured it out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The point of voting is not to ensure that the right person gets elected or that the right ideas get placed in motion, because, as mentioned above, one vote is not really going to make a huge difference. Rather, &lt;i&gt;I think the point of voting is to be aware of the issues and to care about them to the point where you are able to publicly commit to what you believe.&lt;/i&gt; Once you have enough people caring about issues and participating in the argument, then you can finally start seeing great changes that save people, nations, and ideals. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
