<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dream on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/dream/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dream on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/dream/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mental Training, and Learning to Swim</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mental-training-and-learning-to-swim/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mental-training-and-learning-to-swim/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;During my last year at university, I decided to learn to swim. I was reasonably confident in my ability to stay afloat in deep water and not die, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t what you could call swimming. Luckily, two of my close friends were excellent swimmers and they agreed to work with me in the mornings before class.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As an aside, I did take swimming lessons on and off for a few years when I was a kid, but apparently I retained nothing from those classes. Maybe I was just a terrible swimmer the entire time? Possibly related, &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/i-grew-up-in-high-school&#34;&gt;I have very few memories from my elementary and middle school years&lt;/a&gt;, so I have a suspicion that I didn&amp;rsquo;t do a whole lot of thinking when I was a kid. In any case, I was essentially a total beginner to swimming when we started. I knew that you kicked your legs and paddled with your arms to go forward, but that was about it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucid Dreaming</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lucid-dreaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lucid-dreaming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was consistently able to have lucid dreams when I was in high school. Partway through a dream, I would realize that I was dreaming and could then control the rest of the dream to a small extent. As I&amp;rsquo;ve grown older though, this has become less and less common. Maybe age has changed something about my brain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Naturally, I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in lucid dreaming and have read a lot about it. &lt;a href=&#34;https://tim.blog/2009/09/21/how-to-lucid-dream/&#34;&gt;Tim Ferriss has a fascinating beginner&amp;rsquo;s guide on his blog&lt;/a&gt;. Different people seem to have different approaches and theories, so I thought I would write about my own experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
