<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chess on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/chess/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chess on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/chess/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reimagining Chess with AlphaZero</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/reimagining-chess-with-alphazero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/reimagining-chess-with-alphazero/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Modern chess is the culmination of centuries of experience, as well as an evolutionary sequence of rule adjustments from its inception in the 6th century to the modern rules we know today. While classical chess still captivates the minds of millions of players worldwide, the game is anything but static. Many variants have been proposed and played over the years by enthusiasts and theorists. They continue the evolutionary cycle by altering the board, piece placement, or the rules—offering players &amp;ldquo;something subtle, sparkling, or amusing which cannot be done in ordinary chess.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s AlphaZero Destroys Stockfish In 100-Game Match</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/google-s-alphazero-destroys-stockfish-in-100-game-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 22:58:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/google-s-alphazero-destroys-stockfish-in-100-game-match/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Google&amp;rsquo;s AlphaZero program is a machine that plays chess, and it has managed to quickly become the strongest chess AI in the world by implementing machine learning techniques. While existing chess AIs have mostly been massive dictionaries of moves that are put together by humans, AlphaZero learned chess entirely on its own with minimal human input.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I understand it, the hardest part of creating an AI that solves problems like chess is finding some way to calculate if you&amp;rsquo;re winning or not. If that were easy to do, the program could just look at all of its possible moves (which is not very many for a computer) and see which one would leave it winning by more. The trouble is that it&amp;rsquo;s very hard to tell if you&amp;rsquo;re winning. You might need to consider all possible outcomes many moves in advance, which quickly becomes too many to calculate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
