<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Article on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/article/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Article on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The World&#39;s Most Beautiful Data Center</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/the-worlds-most-beautiful-data-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/the-worlds-most-beautiful-data-center/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/torre-girona.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Image: Barcelona Supercomputing Center&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bsc.es/about-bsc/gallery/chapel-torre-girona&#34;&gt;Torre Girona Chapel&lt;/a&gt; was deconsecrated in the 70s, and now houses the MareNostrum supercomputer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We were in need of hundreds of square meters without columns and the capacity to support 44.5 tons of weight,&amp;rdquo; Maspoch told me in an email. &amp;ldquo;At the time there was not much available space at the university and the only room that satisfied our requirements was the Torre Girona chapel. We did not doubt it for a moment and we installed a supercomputer in it.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Materials Science with Machine Learning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/automating-materials-science-with-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/automating-materials-science-with-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A robot arm dips a pipette into a dish and transfers a tiny amount of bright liquid into one of many receptacles sitting in front of another machine. When all the samples are ready, the second machine tests their optical properties, and the results are fed to a computer that controls the arm. Software analyzes the results of these experiments, formulates a few hypotheses, and then starts the process over again. Humans are barely required.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s AlphaZero Destroys Stockfish In 100-Game Match</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/google-s-alphazero-destroys-stockfish-in-100-game-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 22:58:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/google-s-alphazero-destroys-stockfish-in-100-game-match/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Google&amp;rsquo;s AlphaZero program is a machine that plays chess, and it has managed to quickly become the strongest chess AI in the world by implementing machine learning techniques. While existing chess AIs have mostly been massive dictionaries of moves that are put together by humans, AlphaZero learned chess entirely on its own with minimal human input.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I understand it, the hardest part of creating an AI that solves problems like chess is finding some way to calculate if you&amp;rsquo;re winning or not. If that were easy to do, the program could just look at all of its possible moves (which is not very many for a computer) and see which one would leave it winning by more. The trouble is that it&amp;rsquo;s very hard to tell if you&amp;rsquo;re winning. You might need to consider all possible outcomes many moves in advance, which quickly becomes too many to calculate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perils of Eroded Civic Knowledge Forewarned by Former Justice Souter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/perils-of-eroded-civic-knowledge-forewarned-by-fmr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 18:43:32 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/perils-of-eroded-civic-knowledge-forewarned-by-fmr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is extremely important.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pluto - Closest Approach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pluto-closest-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 11:41:17 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pluto-closest-approach/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote class=&#34;twitter-tweet&#34; data-lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&lt;p lang=&#34;en&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Hello &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/hashtag/Pluto?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;#Pluto&lt;/a&gt;! We’re at closest approach. Congrats to all! Follow our story &amp;amp; view new images using &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/hashtag/PlutoFlyby?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;#PlutoFlyby&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;http://t.co/8JVlJrcUkY&#34;&gt;pic.twitter.com/8JVlJrcUkY&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; NASA New Horizons (@NASANewHorizons) &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/NASANewHorizons/status/620923200621412352?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;July 14, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;script async src=&#34;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And here is the best picture we had previously, taken by Hubble. Pretty amazing stuff&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/pluto-hubble-01.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Pluto&#34; width=&#34;400px&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Striking Perspective on New York City Property Values | Metrocosm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/a-striking-perspective-on-new-york-city-property/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 14:17:56 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/a-striking-perspective-on-new-york-city-property/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Property values across the U.S., where the area of each state has been substituted for its total property value.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Night My Girlfriend Dissociated and Forgot Who I Was</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/the-night-my-girlfriend-dissociated-and-forgot-who/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 20:59:26 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/the-night-my-girlfriend-dissociated-and-forgot-who/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Because of her dissociative identity disorder, I was a stranger in the eyes of the woman I loved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beautifully written, and a reminder that something like 50 First Dates is actually a terrifying situation&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Jay’s Magical Secrets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/ricky-jays-magical-secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 16:16:21 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/ricky-jays-magical-secrets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ricky Jay is a legend, and is without a doubt one of my favorite magicians to watch. His shows leave you with a greater appreciation for the magician&amp;rsquo;s craft, rather than just the immediate illusion they present.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homer&#39;s Last Theorem</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/homers-last-theorem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 18:53:41 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/homers-last-theorem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A look into the deep, dark, strangely complicated world of Simpsons mathematics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I knew that Futurama has a lot of great mathematics involved, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize that it started in the Simpsons.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pipino: Gentleman Thief — EPIC MAGAZINE — Medium</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/pipino-gentleman-thief-epic-magazine-medium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 20:27:13 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/pipino-gentleman-thief-epic-magazine-medium/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Magicians, Mafiosos, a Missing Painting, and the Heist of a Lifetime&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Time Everyone &#34;Corrected&#34; the World’s Smartest Woman</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/the-time-everyone-corrected-the-worlds-smartest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 15:40:30 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/the-time-everyone-corrected-the-worlds-smartest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;In 1990, Marilyn vos Savant correctly answered a probability puzzle in her column for Parade Magazine. And then, the world called her an idiot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I still remember the chaos caused by the Monty Hall problem in our high school math class. Here&#39;s my explanation for how it works:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your first choice could either be a car or a goat.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;ol&gt;&#xA;    &lt;li&gt;If you picked the car, you will win the car by not changing your guess.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;    &lt;li&gt;If you picked a goat, the host will reveal the second goat. The last door left will be the car, so you are guaranteed to win if you change your guess.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You have two possible strategies to win the car:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;ol&gt;&#xA;    &lt;li&gt;Try to pick the car on your first guess, and don&#39;t change the guess.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;    &lt;li&gt;Try to pick a goat on your first guess, and change the guess after the host opens another door.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The second strategy is better, since picking a goat is twice as easy as picking the car.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The best strategy is to &lt;em&gt;try to pick a goat&lt;/em&gt; in round 1. Once the host has revealed the second goat, you are guaranteed the car by switching doors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Teenager’s View on Social Media — Backchannel — Medium</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/a-teenagers-view-on-social-media-backchannel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2015 12:16:50 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/a-teenagers-view-on-social-media-backchannel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Very informative description of how teens and college students use the major social networks&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of the Professional Cyber Athlete</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/the-rise-of-the-professional-cyber-athlete/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 19:14:25 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/the-rise-of-the-professional-cyber-athlete/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Very cool profile of Scarlett, a professional StarCraftII player&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relationship Test - Dataclysm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/relationship-test-dataclysm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 15:53:16 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/relationship-test-dataclysm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My team and I wrote an app that will apply findings from a recent research paper to your Facebook graph. The app won’t post to your wall but it will show you both the shape of your friend network and which of your friends are most mathematically important to your life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Instead of looking at a metric like the number of friends you have in common, this algorithm takes it a step further. It looks at how well connected your mutual friends are with each other, and suggests that having more diverse mutual friends indicates a stronger, more important relationship.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Be Polite</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/how-to-be-polite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2014 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/how-to-be-polite/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most people don’t notice I’m polite, which is sort of the point. I don’t look polite. I am big and droopy and need a haircut. No soul would associate me with watercress sandwiches. Still, every year or so someone takes me aside and says, you actually are weirdly polite, aren’t you? And I always thrill. They noticed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Politeness buys you time. It leaves doors open. I’ve met so many people whom, if I had trusted my first impressions, I would never have wanted to meet again. And yet — many of them are now great friends.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobody. Understands. Punctuation.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/nobody-understands-punctuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/nobody-understands-punctuation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://stilldrinking.org/nobody-understands-punctuation&#34;&gt;Peter Welch&lt;/a&gt; has published an excellent piece on punctuation and writing style in the English language.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yes, you can use punctuation in incorrect ways, but that does not mean there is only one way to use it. A friend recently told me publishers don&amp;rsquo;t care whether you use an oxford comma or not, as long as you pick one and stick with it. This is stupid. If punctuation obscures or distorts the meaning of a sentence in an unintended way, it is wrong, but apart from that, punctuation is about rhythm. An Oxford comma is not a flip switch in an author&amp;rsquo;s voice, it&amp;rsquo;s a decision made in the moment to maintain the flow of the idea. Momentum, syncopation, rhythm and pattern make a sentence flow, because writers are trying to transfer the voices in their heads into yours.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Internet With A Human Face</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/the-internet-with-a-human-face/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/the-internet-with-a-human-face/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An excellent talk by Maciej Cegłowski on the bleak state of mass surveillance the internet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco Is Dead. Long Live San Francisco</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/san-francisco-is-dead-long-live-san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/san-francisco-is-dead-long-live-san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.modernluxury.com/san-francisco/story/san-francisco-dead-long-live-san-francisco&#34;&gt;Gary Kamiya&lt;/a&gt; in San Francisco Magazine, talking about the many factors and consequences of San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(I)f present trends continue, the city could soon become a moated citadel of info-money, accessible only to venture capitalists, Twitter engineers, and the creators of hookup apps.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This prospect worries me. As someone who loves San Francisco’s maverick tradition and its class and ethnic diversity (I celebrated both in a book I wrote last year called Cool Gray City of Love), I find the idea that my beloved town is on the verge of becoming another Manhattan—a picturesque but increasingly expensive, homogeneous, and sterile burg—distressing, to put it mildly.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And yet, the political, cultural, and class war that has erupted over what is happening to San Francisco—call it the Change—strikes me as wrongheaded to the point of surreality.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I’m all for rushing the barricades when there’s an enemy to fight and a battle that can be won. I’ve engaged in my share of such battles. But it’s time to reckon with reality: There is no enemy here. Or if there is, it’s an enemy that won’t be defeated. What has hit San Francisco in the last couple of years can be summed up in one word: capitalism. And that is a tsunami that no seawall can keep out.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Gitmo is Killing Me&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/gitmo-is-killing-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 13:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/gitmo-is-killing-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A chilling story told by a prisoner at Guantanamo Bay. I hope that someday we&amp;rsquo;ll look back and wonder how anything like this could have been possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been detained at Guantánamo for 11 years and three months. I have never been charged with any crime. I have never received a trial.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The situation is desperate now. All of the detainees here are suffering deeply. At least 40 people here are on a hunger strike. People are fainting with exhaustion every day. I have vomited blood.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And there is no end in sight to our imprisonment. Denying ourselves food and risking death every day is the choice we have made.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I just hope that because of the pain we are suffering, the eyes of the world will once again look to Guantánamo before it is too late.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea missle launch delayed by Windows 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/north-korea-missle-launch-delayed-by-windows-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/north-korea-missle-launch-delayed-by-windows-8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;#OnionOrActualHeadline&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The announcement from the Korean Central News Agency (KCNA) did not indicate a new scheduled time for a missile test, saying only that it was “working with Windows 8 support to resolve the issue.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A source close to the North Korean regime reported that Supreme Leader Kim Jong-un is furious about the Windows 8 problems and is considering a number of options, including declaring war on Microsoft.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrono Trigger Retrospective</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/chrono-trigger-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/chrono-trigger-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Chrono Trigger basically began as a jam session — a couple of star designers and a manga artist getting together to brainstorm and seeing what they might produce. No pressure. No cynicism.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[ . . . ]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, the best thing about Chrono Trigger is something that can’t quite be quantified in terms of mechanics, aesthetics, or plot. It’s impossible to play without getting the sense that that its designers really had a lot of fun in conceiving it (barring a stomach ulcer or two) and were wholly dedicated to making sure they got it right. Chrono Trigger is a labor of love effected by a group of very talented game designers, and their enthusiasm for the project permeates every aspect of the experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Boy Named Sue, and a Theory of Names</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/a-boy-named-sue-and-a-theory-of-names/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 05:08:49 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/a-boy-named-sue-and-a-theory-of-names/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What will you name your child? &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donkey Kong and Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/donkey-kong-and-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 03:22:41 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/donkey-kong-and-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An excellent story about the making of Donkey Kong and what it was like to work in an early video game company. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterations of Google&#39;s logo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/iterations-of-googles-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 17:43:59 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/iterations-of-googles-logo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m definitely glad they keep iterating until they got to the current version, but that 2nd revision&amp;rsquo;s pretty neat too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple sets the design standard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/apple-sets-the-design-standard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 03:49:29 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/apple-sets-the-design-standard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A pretty good article describing Apple&amp;rsquo;s success with their high attention to design.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buy a mac</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/buy-a-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2008 05:00:30 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/buy-a-mac/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article is so strange. It shows all the reasons why buying a PC with Windows Vista is a terrible idea, and yet the author seems perfectly happy with his Vista computer, even after paying absurd amounts of money to fix something that shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have broke in the first place.  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
