<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Language on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/language/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Language on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 03:13:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/language/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Journaling in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/journal-2025.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;An image of my Rollbahn notebook. It features an illustration of a train on Japan&amp;rsquo;s Odakyu line.&#34; title=&#34;2025 Journal&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2025 was the first year that I maintained a physical journal for the entire year. I had never been able to continue the habit, and admired people who could. My goal was pretty simple – at the end of the year, have a journal that I wrote in consistently for 12 months. This has been a success!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful vs. Effective Prose</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/beautiful-vs.-effective-prose/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/beautiful-vs.-effective-prose/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A long time ago, I fancied myself a writer and strove to write beautiful prose. I read a lot and borrowed from styles that I admired, but oftentimes my sentences ran on, and I relied on my thesaurus too heavily. But I enjoyed the process of writing and reached a familiarity with words that allowed me to simply let my thoughts flow through my fingers onto the page.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At university, I discovered &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Elements_of_Style&#34;&gt;The Elements of Style&lt;/a&gt; and quickly became an advocate instead of lean, effective prose. I strove to convey my thoughts using fewer words. Composition took more effort as I scrutinized each phrase. I was happy with the results, and I felt a deliberate craftsmanship that seemed more pronounced than before.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
