<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:47:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Static site generator wishlist</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/static-site-generator-wishlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:47:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/static-site-generator-wishlist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A list of things I want to prioritize when choosing and customizing whatever static-site generator I use for building this site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently using: &lt;a href=&#34;https://jekyllrb.com/&#34;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;, but not enthusiastically&#xA;Next contender: &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-just-let-me-write-my-words&#34;&gt;1. Just let me write my words&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve recently realized that including software-specific text in my post and pages creates a lot of mental overhead. I make use of a number of handy shortcode functions. For example, creating an image block with descriptions and alt code, with an optional caption using &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; if I want to provide extra commentary or link back to the source. This is handy, but there are two big problems:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t min-max your hobbies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/min-max-hobbies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:51:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/min-max-hobbies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I’m having fun with a hobby, nothing kills my motivation faster than learning about a better, more efficient way I could be doing things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was playing Fantasy Life i – chopping trees, making boots, fishing fish, and just generally having a grand time. It felt like alchemy skills were taking longer than the rest to level up, so i checked a wiki to see if i was missing something. Big mistake. What i learned is that, if i haven’t created 4 sunglasses with EXP boost buffs and then started crafting 10 thousand health potions to power level, I’m wasting my time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buy local</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/buy-local/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/buy-local/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I look at reviews before buying things, and I prefer personal websites and youtube channels over large publications because I can get a feel for the person behind the opinions, and their preferences. I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed though that reviews gravitate towards a certain subset of good, but mostly American brands. This is only a problem because I live in Japan, where limited availability and terrible exchange rates makes everything feel twice as expensive as they ought to be.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Favorites – 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/media-favorites-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/media-favorites-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Looking back on the media I consumed in 2025, this is a list of just my favorites.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-games&#34;&gt;🎮️ Games&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;dragon-quest-v&#34;&gt;Dragon Quest V&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was always a Nintendo kid, and have played very few &lt;em&gt;Dragon Quest&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Final Fantasy&lt;/em&gt; games. I&amp;rsquo;d heard that is one of the best, and I finally grabbed the iOS port this year. Among other things, I was really impressed by the clever usage of game mechanics to tell story.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journaling in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/journal-2025.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;An image of my Rollbahn notebook. It features an illustration of a train on Japan&amp;rsquo;s Odakyu line.&#34; title=&#34;2025 Journal&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2025 was the first year that I maintained a physical journal for the entire year. I had never been able to continue the habit, and admired people who could. My goal was pretty simple – at the end of the year, have a journal that I wrote in consistently for 12 months. This has been a success!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I was hacked!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hacked/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 05:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hacked/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.jakesaunders.dev/my-server-started-mining-monero-this-morning/&#34;&gt;Jake Saunders wrote&lt;/a&gt; about discovering that a recent Next.js vulnerability allowed hackers access to their server through an Umami instance. I use Umami, too!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I logged into my VPS and didn&amp;rsquo;t see any suspicious files or running processes. I then opened my Umami dashboard to poke around, and my browser immediately opened a window to a gambling site. Well, shit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;damage-assessment&#34;&gt;Damage assessment&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The browser&amp;rsquo;s developer console showed that an &lt;code&gt;onclick&lt;/code&gt; event was added to the &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;html&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; object, and this was originating from a file disguised to look like a standard Next.js library file used by Umami. So the attacker was able to modify and add files, as well as spoof the modified date to hide their tracks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transparent leadership</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/transparent-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:11:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/transparent-leadership/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href=&#34;https://entropicthoughts.com/transparent-leadership-beats-servant-leadership&#34;&gt;Transparent Leadership Beats Servant Leadership&lt;/a&gt;, by Chris at &lt;a href=&#34;https://entropicthoughts.com/index&#34;&gt;Entropic Thoughts&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my book, a good leader&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;coaches people,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;connects people,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[. . .]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;creates direct links between supply and demand (instead of deliberately making themselves a middle man),&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[. . .]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;generally makes themselves redundant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I really related with many of the points in this post. Coincidentally, I had just recently come to some similar conclusions at my own workplace, too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rambling about — Keyboards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/r-keyboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:36:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/r-keyboards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I use an &lt;a href=&#34;https://iqunix.com/products/magi65&#34;&gt;IQUNIX Magi65&lt;/a&gt; keyboard at home, and absolutely love it. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get the Pro version, as I don&amp;rsquo;t really need a dial or media keys, and I preferred the smaller size anyways. The only real criticism I noticed in reviews was that the keyboard is pretty heavy, but this turned out to be a good thing for me. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to carry the thing around with me, and I love the solidity as I type. The typing experience is fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copy and paste across Google Slides</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/paste-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 10:31:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/paste-slides/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I wanted to copy slides from one Google Slide document to another. Half-expecting it to not work, I just copied slides in one document, switched to a different tab, hit paste&amp;hellip; and it worked! Seamless and perfect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It looks like when you copy slides, your clipboard actually saves a special payload that contains information about the slides you are copying, rather than the raw content. Then when you paste that into a Slides document, it retrieves the slide data from its servers and imports them to the second document. I imagine you have to be logged into the same Google account in both tabs for it to work properly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To experience, rather than record</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/experience-record/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:21:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/experience-record/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.joanwestenberg.com/p/i-deleted-my-second-brain&#34;&gt;Joan Westenberg&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PKM systems promise coherence, but they often deliver a kind of abstracted confusion. The more I wrote into my vault, the less I felt. A quote would spark an insight, I’d clip it, tag it, link it - and move on. But the insight was never lived. It was stored. Like food vacuum-sealed and never eaten, while any nutritional value slips away.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I first started using PKM tools, I believed I was solving a problem of forgetting. Later, I believed I was solving a problem of integration. Eventually, I realized I had created a new problem: deferral. The more my system grew, the more I deferred the work of thought to some future self who would sort, tag, distill, and extract the gold.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication-driven productivity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 15:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cdp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Or, &amp;ldquo;The latest chapter in my fool&amp;rsquo;s quest to discover a productivity framework that magically makes me effortlessly productive&amp;rdquo;. So it goes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always considered my todo list as a list of things I need to do (for obvious reasons). But I had a minor epiphany and realized that, in my current role, everything I do has exactly zero value &lt;em&gt;until I communicate it to the right people&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example: One big item on my todo list now is to finish writing a proposal for improving how we evaluate new game ideas. But if the overarching objective is &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;Improve how we evaluate new game ideas&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;, the direct actions to achieve this are &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;Convince the right important people and get approval&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;, followed by &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;Tell everybody about the changes&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;. These are accompanied by the prerequisite sub-tasks, &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;Write up a convincing proposal&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;Update the existing guideline documents&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bike rides for my wandering mind</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/bike-rides-wandering-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:51:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/bike-rides-wandering-mind/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My daily commute includes a 20-minute bike ride to the train station. I started this as a way to keep my body moving, but I&amp;rsquo;ve come to love it for the freedom it gives my mind. I can think about whatever I want to, but it&amp;rsquo;s also all right to not think about anything.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The weather is nice today, and I listen to the birds talking at one another.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The sun has started getting higher in the sky when I leave, so I&amp;rsquo;ll probably want to start wearing my sunglasses again soon.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos of Japan that haven&#39;t changed in 150 years</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/old-japan-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:18:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/old-japan-photos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was pointed to an &lt;a href=&#34;https://cosmographia.substack.com/p/photographs-of-old-japan&#34;&gt;article on Cosmographia&lt;/a&gt; which in turn shared &lt;a href=&#34;https://sova.si.edu/record/fsa.a1999.35?s=0&amp;amp;n=10&amp;amp;t=C&amp;amp;q=japan&amp;amp;i=1&#34;&gt;an archive of photos taken in 19th century Japan&lt;/a&gt;. These are amazing photos, but what struck me was how &lt;em&gt;familiar&lt;/em&gt; some of them felt. Photos taken from 150 years ago should feel like looking into another world, but some of these scenes, the architecture, are still very present today. It makes it clear how cultural artifacts are so remarkably well-preserved here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you love something, pay a subscription fee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pay-a-subscription/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:39:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pay-a-subscription/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a rule of thumb, you are more likely to be satisfied by a service that you pay for directly. This is because paying money makes you a &lt;em&gt;customer&lt;/em&gt; of the business, and the business is thereby directly motivated to keep you satisfied.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you want to find a service that will satisfy you for a long time, &lt;em&gt;paying a subscription&lt;/em&gt; is your best bet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are some facts:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In general, a business aims to please its customers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A business&amp;rsquo;s customers are &lt;em&gt;those who pay it money&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you do not pay money to a business, you are not its customer.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A user of a service who does not pay is, strictly speaking, not a customer. In most cases, the needs of the user and the needs of the customer are not too far apart, so many non-paying users are generally satisfied. But on average, in the long run, the needs of the non-user customer and the needs of the non-customer users will drift apart.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity and Community on the Fediverse</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/identity-vs-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 14:23:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/identity-vs-community/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://fediverse.info&#34;&gt;The Fediverse&lt;/a&gt;, a network of interconnected social media services, requires users to choose a service for their account, tying their identity to that community. This can be problematic if the community experiences issues like spam, moderation problems, or shutdown. If we could decouple identity from community, like Reddit did with subreddits, users could more freely participate in multiple communities — and the network overall would be more accessible and resilient.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When a music festival was cancelled, idol fans supported the local community</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/momokuro-fans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:44:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/momokuro-fans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some uplifting &lt;a href=&#34;https://news.yahoo.co.jp/articles/f3dc7027f17ec3d90e0da75d8f622e12452f471a&#34;&gt;news from Japan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On April 13th in Shibata City of Niigata prefecture (Japan), the popular idol group &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.momoclo.net&#34;&gt;Momoiro Clover Z&lt;/a&gt; had been planning a large music festival in cooperation with a large number of other artists, as well as local police, schools, and city government. However, on the day of festival the weather took a turn for the worse, and warnings were issued for strong winds, flash floods, and avalanches.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A website redesign</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/redesign-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 14:02:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/redesign-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve overhauled the design of my website, and am very happy with how it turned out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/2025/index-redesign.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The root homepage. Old design on the left, new design on the right.&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#39;http://localhost:1313/images/2025/dark-redesign.jpg&#39; alt=&#39;A post page in dark mode. Old design on the left, new design on the right.&#39; class=&#34;center-image&#34; style=&#34;max-height: 300px;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;    &lt;figcaption&gt;A post page in dark mode. Old design on the left, new design on the right.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;design-considerations&#34;&gt;Design considerations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-structure&#34;&gt;The structure&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My first inspiration was the concept of &lt;a href=&#34;https://slashpages.net&#34;&gt;slash pages&lt;/a&gt;, which I love — they are very easy to understand, and have a fun vibe characteristic of simple webpages that are just collections of pages. I wanted to take it a step further, and use the structure of the website as a design feature. The navigation element is arranged like a file system, and the current page&amp;rsquo;s URL is displayed prominently in the header.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I may have outgrown Coolify</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/outgrowing-coolify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 13:35:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/outgrowing-coolify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I initially chose &lt;a href=&#34;https://coolify.io/&#34;&gt;Coolify&lt;/a&gt; as a self-hosted alternative to Heroku when it got too expensive. Coolify makes a lot of things very easy, but I ended up having to dig in to the details and learn a lot to fix things that didn&amp;rsquo;t work. Now that I have learned a fair bit about server management, I&amp;rsquo;ve found that I may no longer need Coolify&amp;rsquo;s hand-holding.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;venturing-into-self-hosting&#34;&gt;Venturing into self-hosting&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I knew next to nothing about Linux servers, Docker, reverse proxies, and the like. I had used Heroku for a long time, but its base price became restrictively expensive considering how small each of my little projects was, so I started looking for a service that could ease me into self-hosting my apps on a VPS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My AI manifesto</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ai-manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:55:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ai-manifesto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my personal manifesto for how I will and will not use generative AI. I believe it can be an extremely useful tool in certain situations, but can also have many negative repurcussions if used incorrectly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-use-to-expand-my-abilities-not-as-a-crutch&#34;&gt;1: Use to expand my abilities, not as a crutch.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-teach-me-new-things&#34;&gt;A: Teach me new things&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a coding assistant, AI can quickly show me the correct syntax. It can suggest implementations, and teach me how to implement new functions. These are extremely useful, and help me to be exponentionally more productive as a hobby developer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Photo Composition Challenge</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-compo-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:56:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-compo-challenge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a mediocre photographer at best, but of course I want to improve. When I saw that &lt;a href=&#34;https://social.lol/@hiro&#34;&gt;@hiro&lt;/a&gt; was putting together 5-week challenge to experiment with various compositional techniques and share our photos, I had to join.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t have fancy gear, or a lot of time to go hunting for photos, so almost all of my shots were scenes from my daily life, taken with an iPhone. I realized pretty quickly though, that being deliberate about composition gave a new perspective on even familiar scenes, and I was surprised at compelling some of the photos turned out.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python script failing via cron</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/python-cron/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 15:11:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/python-cron/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-issue&#34;&gt;The issue&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had setup a cron task to run my &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/2025/01/09/squirrel-archive-webpages-so-i-can-find-them-again.html&#34;&gt;Squirrel Archiver&lt;/a&gt; script once per day, but for some reason the task was not executing. Nothing, including any errors, was showing up in any logs. At first I thought there was something wrong with my crontab, but other scripts set up to run in the same way were running without issue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Copying the commands in crontab to the terminal and running it manually worked. It was only when cron was triggering the run that it failed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrossPooter - Poot your toots around the web</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/crosspooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 16:57:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/crosspooter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/projects/crosspooter.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;CrossPooter logo, showing a smiling cartoon face among arrows branching away&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CrossPooter is a simple script for personal use, that reads the RSS feed of this website and posts the latest article to GoToSocial and Bluesky. It was inspired by &lt;a href=&#34;https://echofeed.app&#34;&gt;EchoFeed&lt;/a&gt;, but I wanted to try my hand at making something similar myself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can see the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/aonsager/crosspooter&#34;&gt;source code here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CrossPooter reads the RSS feed of this website and checks if the latest article has been posted yet. If not, it will grab the article&amp;rsquo;s OpenGraph tags to construct a post.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The geometric nests of the white-spotted pufferfish</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-geometric-nests-of-the-white-spotted-pufferfish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:25:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-geometric-nests-of-the-white-spotted-pufferfish/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The white-spotted pufferfish, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://amami-horizon.com/en/nature/ocean/amami-hoshizorafugu&#34;&gt;Amami hoshizora fugu&lt;/a&gt;, is a species of pufferfish newly discovered in 2014 near Japan&amp;rsquo;s Amami-Oshima Island. The males spend roughly a week constructing an elaborate circular nest about 2 meters in diameter to attract females.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Divers had known about these structures that appear in early summer every year, but apparently it took a while to catch the fish in action.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/2025/whitespottedpuffer_nest.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The circular nest of the white-spotted pufferfish&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hobbies that I am no good at</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hobbies-that-i-am-no-good-at/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:48:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hobbies-that-i-am-no-good-at/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A distinguished actor appeared on TV and talked about their love for juggling. They had taken lessons at various times and always sets aside time to practice because they enjoy it so much. They then recounted how they recently met their juggling teacher of ~10 years past, displayed their current juggling skills, and was met with astonishment at how &lt;em&gt;they had not improved one bit in all that time!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was a funny story, but what struck me was just how &lt;em&gt;nice&lt;/em&gt; it was that juggling was a constant source of enjoyment for this person &lt;em&gt;despite apparently being no good at it&lt;/em&gt;. That&amp;rsquo;s a hard thing to do.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sociable Weaver</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-sociable-weaver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-sociable-weaver/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sociable_weaver&#34;&gt;sociable weaver&lt;/a&gt; is an African bird that creates giant, community nests in trees. The nests look like a giant woolly mammoth hanging in a tree, and have many entry holes on the bottom. These nests can house over 100 pairs of birds, spanning multiple generations at a time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/2025/sociable_weaver.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Photo from Wikipedia, by Harald Süpfle&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a parent introduced me to stress</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/becoming-a-parent-introduced-me-to-stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/becoming-a-parent-introduced-me-to-stress/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have always been a calm and happy person. Aggressively optimistic, even. I made it through the first 1/3 of my life without feeling much stress, only getting angry on rare occasions. Anger management, emotional therapy, mindfulness exercises, these were all things that I had no need for.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I thought that this was a personality trait, but now I realize that I was simply blessed with an easy life. It&amp;rsquo;s not that I was particularly good at dealing with stress, I just didn&amp;rsquo;t have much stress coming my way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squirrel - Archive webpages so I can find them again</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/squirrel---archive-webpages-so-i-can-find-them-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/squirrel---archive-webpages-so-i-can-find-them-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/2025/squirrel.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/aonsager/squirrel-archiver&#34;&gt;created a thing&lt;/a&gt; that lets me save webpage contents in a smart way. I know, there are a million bookmark managers and web archivers out there, but this one is for me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-motivation&#34;&gt;The Motivation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href=&#34;https://pinboard.in/about/&#34;&gt;Pinboard&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do you half-remember interesting things you saw online six months ago, but struggle to find them in a search engine?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yes, yes, a hundred times yes. This happens to me all the time. Searching my history doesn&amp;rsquo;t work because usually the keywords I remember are not in the title. Google et al. aren&amp;rsquo;t much help either.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebranding the site: Invisible Parade</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/rebranding-the-site-invisible-parade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/rebranding-the-site-invisible-parade/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I first started this personal website just about 20 years ago. It began as a couple of html pages, and spent time as a Wordpress blog, a Tumblr page, and is now a static blog generated by Jekyll. Through that time, it had always just had my name, alexonsager.com. This year, I’m rebranding it to &lt;strong&gt;Invisible Parade&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;being-online-then&#34;&gt;Being online then&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I started this site I had just entered university, got my first MacBook, and was excited to become a full-fledged citizen of the internet. At the time, I thought it was cool to publish as much of yourself as possible. Tag yourself and your friends in the photos you take, scrobble the music you listen to, check in to the places you go, tweet your thoughts. Since I was broadcasting myself to the world, it made sense to put my name on my website. That’s how people would know me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing GoToSocial on Coolify</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-gotosocial-on-coolify/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-gotosocial-on-coolify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Following up to my &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/2024/12/02/i-want-to-love-mastodon.html&#34;&gt;earlier post about the fediverse&lt;/a&gt;, I discovered &lt;a href=&#34;https://gotosocial.org&#34;&gt;GoToSocial&lt;/a&gt;. Compared to Mastodon which required a fair amount of server overhead (more than I could justify for just playing around online), GoToSocial is very &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.gotosocial.org/en/latest/getting_started/#server-vps&#34;&gt;lightweight&lt;/a&gt;: 1 CPU, 1GB memory, and 15GB-20GB of storage space for the first year or so. Sold!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This would let me set up my own single-user server, which solves all of my misgivings about Mastodon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;callout&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;I am a total novice at all things server-related! I am probably at least a little bit wrong about some of the things I write here. Please take my experience with a grain of salt, and correct me if you can.&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have a VPS with &lt;a href=&#34;https://coolify.io&#34;&gt;Coolify&lt;/a&gt; to manage the multiple apps I have running, and all things considered it makes things very easy.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I used a docker-compose file to deploy GoToSocial, and their &lt;a href=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/superseriousbusiness/gotosocial/main/example/docker-compose/docker-compose.yaml&#34;&gt;example file&lt;/a&gt; was almost perfect as-is.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adguard was preventing sites from loading in Safari sometimes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/adguard-was-preventing-sites-from-loading-in-safari-sometimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/adguard-was-preventing-sites-from-loading-in-safari-sometimes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For some reason, some sites would not load in Safari. Certain assets, often hosted on a CDN but not always, would hang forever and keep the page from loading. Other browsers worked, curl worked, so it didn&amp;rsquo;t seem like a DNS issue. It was driving me crazy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think I finally caught the culprit: Adguard&amp;rsquo;s network filtering.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adguard gives you the option to filter all of your internet traffic for various apps on your computer. By default, it does so through a &amp;ldquo;Network Extension&amp;rdquo; that registers a local VPN to filter all traffic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I want to love Mastodon...</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/i-want-to-love-mastodon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/i-want-to-love-mastodon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;But it&amp;rsquo;s just not doing it for me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[!NOTE] Update 2024/12/27&#xA;I have set up my own instance of GoToSocial, and have written about it [[installing-gotosocial-on-coolify | here]].&#xA;This seems like the best solution for me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The main selling point of Mastodon is its &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.joinmastodon.org/#federation&#34;&gt;federation&lt;/a&gt; I think, and I tend to agree with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tbray.org/ongoing/When/202x/2024/11/15/Not-Bluesky&#34;&gt;Tim Bray&amp;rsquo;s points&lt;/a&gt; that some kind of decentralized, protocol-based network for social exchange is what will endure. Having one service run by one group of people is brittle. Having many services run by many groups of people is resilient.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comments are back</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/comments-are-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/comments-are-back/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This site has gone through many forms, and comments have come and gone. Now they are back, made possible by &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/souramoo/commentoplusplus&#34;&gt;commento++&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;https://commento.io&#34;&gt;Commento&lt;/a&gt; was popular and on my radar for a while, but the original repository has been dead for a while. Commento++ is a fork that has been dead for&amp;hellip; a little bit less of a while. But it has a few improvements from the original, and as long as it&amp;rsquo;s stable I don&amp;rsquo;t care so much.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing Python3 modules on Macs in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-python3-modules-on-macs-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-python3-modules-on-macs-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When trying to install python modules on a new Mac, I kept getting thwarted by this error:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;error: externally-managed-environment&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;× This environment is externally managed&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;╰─&amp;gt; To install Python packages system-wide, try brew install&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    xyz, where xyz is the package you are trying to&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    install.&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    &#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    If you wish to install a non-brew-packaged Python package,&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    create a virtual environment using python3 -m venv path/to/venv.&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    Then use path/to/venv/bin/python and path/to/venv/bin/pip.&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    &#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    If you wish to install a non-brew packaged Python application,&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    it may be easiest to use pipx install xyz, which will manage a&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    virtual environment &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;for&lt;/span&gt; you. Make sure you have pipx installed.&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;note: If you believe this is a mistake, please contact your Python installation or OS distribution provider. You can override this, at the risk of breaking your Python installation or OS, by passing --break-system-packages.&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hint: See PEP &lt;span style=&#34;color:#ae81ff&#34;&gt;668&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;for&lt;/span&gt; the detailed specification.&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems like installing modules into a virtual environment is the way to go, which is what I had been doing for individual applications, but I wanted to be able to run this script from Alred workflows.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Links - November 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-links---november-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-links---november-2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;dl&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://anlucas.neocities.org/88x31Buttons.html&#34;&gt;A.N. Lucas&#39;s 88x31 button Collection&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(anlucas.neocities.org)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;A collection of classic web banner images.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.howtogeek.com/830179/how-to-run-stable-diffusion-on-your-pc-to-generate-ai-images/&#34;&gt;How to Run Stable Diffusion on Your PC to Generate AI Images&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(www.howtogeek.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;For personal reference.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uL0atQFZzL8&#34;&gt;If You Can&#39;t Answer These 6 Questions You Don&#39;t Have A Story - Glenn Gers&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(www.youtube.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;The essence of a story is a character trying to accomplish something while people or things get in their way. Every character (not just the main one) is trying to accomplish something, and narrative is born each time they collide and get bumped off track, like billiard balls.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dl&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Links - October 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-links---october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-links---october-2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;dl&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gamedeveloper.com/design/how-to-make-a-roguelike&#34;&gt;How to Make a Roguelike&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(www.gamedeveloper.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;Practical tips for how to plan and structure a new Roguelike game.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hackster.io/news/this-novel-mechanical-neural-network-architected-material-learns-to-respond-to-its-environment-ad68bdcf2d7b&#34;&gt;&#34;Mechanical Neural Network&#34; Learns to Respond to Its Environment&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(www.hackster.io)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;Flexible parts within a pattern of beams move and bend by reacting to magnetic fields. Future uses may include efficient aircraft wings or earthquake-resistant buildings.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://variety.com/2022/tv/news/william-shatner-space-boldly-go-excerpt-1235395113/&#34;&gt;William Shatner: My Trip to Space Filled Me With Sadness&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(variety.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;Expecting beauty, William Shatner looked out into space and saw only death. Life and beauty only exists on Earth, and its tininess and fragility was overwhelming.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://jalammar.github.io/illustrated-stable-diffusion/&#34;&gt;The Illustrated Stable Diffusion&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(jalammar.github.io)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;An illustrated guide explaining how Stable Diffusion works&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://coolify.io/&#34;&gt;Coolify&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(coolify.io)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;An open-source &amp; self-hostable Heroku / Netlify alternative&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://thereformedbroker.com/2022/10/02/you-werent-supposed-to-see-that/&#34;&gt;You weren&#39;t supposed to see that&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(thereformedbroker.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;Powerful economic stimulus during the pandemic worked a little too well and made everyone&#39;s lives better. But we need to have both winners and losers, so now were are backpedaling to bring things back to normal, i.e. worse for the bottom rung.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dl&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obsidian iCloud sync between Mac and iPhone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/obsidian-icloud-sync-between-mac-and-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/obsidian-icloud-sync-between-mac-and-iphone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just using iCloud sync has been pretty solid in my experience. I have two Macs and one iPhone that share a single vault, and I&amp;rsquo;ve had no major issues&amp;hellip; except for one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Because the entire Obsidian folder lives inside of iCloud, the &lt;code&gt;.obsidian&lt;/code&gt; settings folder is also synced. Usually a good thing, except that the multi-pane view I have setup for desktop keeps getting pushed onto mobile. Because the panes all become tiny, and because Obsidian reverts to this view every time I use the app on desktop again, Obsidian basically became unusable on my phone.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Links - September 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-links---september-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-links---september-2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;dl&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/RootMyTV/RootMyTV.github.io&#34;&gt;RootMyTV&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(RootMyTV.github.io)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;A user-friendly exploit for rooting/jailbreaking LG webOS smart TVs.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lamag.com/citythinkblog/zodiac-killer-paul-alfred-doerr/&#34;&gt;Has The Zodiac Killer Mystery Been Solved (Again)&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(www.lamag.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/LambdaLabsML/examples/tree/main/stable-diffusion-finetuning&#34;&gt;examples/stable-diffusion-finetuning at main · LambdaLabsML/examples&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(github.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;Fine tune Stable Diffusion to generate pokemon images&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://brickit.app/&#34;&gt;Brickit&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(brickit.app)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;App scans a pile of your legos and gives you ideas to create, complete with detailed instructions.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://twofergoofer.com/&#34;&gt;Twofer Goofer&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(twofergoofer.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;Guess a pair of rhyming words based on their fictional definition.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://experimentalhistory.substack.com/p/excuse-me-but-why-are-you-eating&#34;&gt;Excuse me but why are you eating so many frogs&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(experimentalhistory.substack.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;Productivity hacks imply that you can trick yourself into doing things you don&#39;t want to do, in favor of things you&#39;d rather be doing. The author suggests that maybe you should instead stop forcing yourself to do so many unpleasant things.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fast.ai/2022/09/06/homeschooling/&#34;&gt;My family&#39;s unlikely homeschooling journey · fast.ai&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(www.fast.ai)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;The pandemic forced this family into experimenting with homeschooling. With good resources and a strong local support system, they found that their new arrangement seemed to work better for their kids than traditional schools do.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dl&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Links - August 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-links---august-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-links---august-2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;dl&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://rentry.org/SDInstallGuide&#34;&gt;Stable Diffusion install guide&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(rentry.org)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;Install and run Stable Diffusion locally&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://sambleckley.com/writing/church-of-interruption.html&#34;&gt;The Church of Interruption&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(sambleckley.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;There are four conversational styles, divided on two axes. Most people who interrupt others are willing to be interrupted themselves, while other people dislike interrupting and being interrupted. These fundamental differences can cause awkwardness in conversation.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dt&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;https://diagrams.app/&#34;&gt;Diagrams: A Native Diagram Editor for Mac&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(diagrams.app)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;  &lt;dd&gt;I was just looking for a good way to create flowcharts, and this looks just right&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dl&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web links - July 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-links---july-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-links---july-2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;dl&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;a href=&#34;https://edition.cnn.com/style/article/magic-mirror-cincinnati-art-museum-scn/index.html&#34;&gt;Magic mirror&#39;: Hidden image revealed in reflection of centuries-old artifact at Cincinnati Art Museum&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(edition.cnn.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dd&gt;A seemingly blank bronze mirror reflects an image of Buddha when shining a bright light onto it. Aside from how amazing it is that this was discovered, the craftsmanship is incredible.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;a href=&#34;https://johnedchristensen.github.io/WebbCompare/&#34;&gt;Compare Webb&#39;s Images to Hubble&#39;s&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(johnedchristensen.github.io)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dd&gt;Yes the images from the Webb telescope are beautiful, but direct comparisons like this really put it into perspective. And this shows the galaxy cluster as it was 4.6 billion years ago? I don&#39;t even know what to think about that.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;a href=&#34;https://seandietrich.com/mendon-missouri/&#34;&gt;Mendon, Missouri - Sean of the South&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(seandietrich.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dd&gt;A short telling of how residents of a small town came together to help the victims of a rail road accident.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dl&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web links - June 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-links---june-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-links---june-2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;dl&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;a href=&#34;http://colinmorris.github.io/blog/compound-curse-words&#34;&gt;Compound pejoratives on Reddit – from &lt;i&gt;buttface&lt;/i&gt; to &lt;i&gt;wankpuffin&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(colinmorris.github.io)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dd&gt;A thorough analysis of the distribution of derogatory terms used on Reddit. Fascinating and hilarious.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;a href=&#34;https://nautil.us/my-out_of_body-experience-13509/&#34;&gt;My Out-of-Body Experience - Nautilus&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(nautil.us)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dd&gt;Reflections on the author&#39;s experience in a sensory deprivation tank.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;a href=&#34;https://prompt.press/&#34;&gt;prompt.press - AI generated artwork inspired by current events&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(prompt.press)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dd&gt;The author mentioned that these are heavily curated, but nonetheless they are extremely compelling.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.grumpygamer.com/rtmi_trailer&#34;&gt;Grumpy Gamer - Return to Monkey Island Trailer&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(www.grumpygamer.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;a href=&#34;https://serendeputy.com/about&#34;&gt;Serendeputy: Newsfeed Engine for the open web&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(serendeputy.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dd&gt;I&#39;ve been thinking about a product like this for a very long time, so it must be a good idea. Depends heavily on who you follow though, so I would probably end up creating a separate account.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;dt&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sixthtone.com/news/1010653/she-spent-a-decade-writing-fake-russian-history.-wikipedia-just-noticed.-?source=channel_rising&#34;&gt;She Spent a Decade Writing Fake Russian History. Wikipedia Just Noticed.&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;span class=&#34;post-meta&#34;&gt;(www.sixthtone.com)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dl&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sorry the Elevator is Crowded</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sorry-the-elevator-is-crowded/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sorry-the-elevator-is-crowded/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The elevator in our office building has a small LCD panel that shows information like the current floor, but when the total weight of passengers crosses a certain threshold it also adds a short note: &amp;ldquo;Sorry the elevator is crowded&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It struck me – of all possible features for an elevator display, how did they decide that they needed this one? It has no impact on the elevator&amp;rsquo;s function of moving people vertically. And a crowded elevator is not the elevator&amp;rsquo;s fault (although this is most likely just an example of Japan&amp;rsquo;s self-deprecating approach to hospitality). So why was this message deemed necessary?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procrastination and Fear of Failure</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/procrastination-and-fear-of-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/procrastination-and-fear-of-failure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I tend to procrastinate if I let myself, so I&amp;rsquo;ve tried my share of techniques to keep it in check. At some point, I read that a fear of failure can cause procrastination, and this really resonated with me. Realizing this has helped me understand where my urge to put things off is coming from.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If I have a large task in front of me, my mind rushes through everything that needs to be done and affirms how difficult it will be. I imagine (mostly subconsciously) all the ways that my output will be less than ideal, and that is what keeps me from taking action.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music of the City - an Art Project Idea</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/music-of-the-city---an-art-project-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/music-of-the-city---an-art-project-idea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve had an idea for a fun art project in my head for many years now, and I don&amp;rsquo;t see myself going through with it any time soon, so I&amp;rsquo;ll compromise by just writing about it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The idea is to photograph people (with permission) who are wearing headphones in the city. Their photo will be shown along with the song they happened to be listening to. It would be interesting to see if a viewer would see any correlation between a person&amp;rsquo;s visual appearance and their taste in music. The prompt &amp;ldquo;What song was playing right now&amp;rdquo; is much more interesting than &amp;ldquo;What is your favorite music,&amp;rdquo; and some people might think that I caught them at just the wrong time, making things more fun for me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Father&#39;s Bookshelf</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-fathers-bookshelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-fathers-bookshelf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For a long time, I&amp;rsquo;ve avoided collecting too much stuff. I buy Kindle versions of books whenever possible, but there is a small shelf for the few books I have carried around with me over the years. My son, who is not quite two years old, will sometimes rummage through my books and leave them in a heap once he realizes there are no pictures, but it made me remember what my own father&amp;rsquo;s bookshelf was like for me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful vs. Effective Prose</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/beautiful-vs.-effective-prose/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/beautiful-vs.-effective-prose/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A long time ago, I fancied myself a writer and strove to write beautiful prose. I read a lot and borrowed from styles that I admired, but oftentimes my sentences ran on, and I relied on my thesaurus too heavily. But I enjoyed the process of writing and reached a familiarity with words that allowed me to simply let my thoughts flow through my fingers onto the page.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At university, I discovered &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Elements_of_Style&#34;&gt;The Elements of Style&lt;/a&gt; and quickly became an advocate instead of lean, effective prose. I strove to convey my thoughts using fewer words. Composition took more effort as I scrutinized each phrase. I was happy with the results, and I felt a deliberate craftsmanship that seemed more pronounced than before.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit: Become Human</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/detroit-become-human/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/detroit-become-human/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/2020/detroit.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;aside&#34;&gt;In this review, I&#39;ll talk about a few parts of the game that stood out to me, and I&#39;ll do my best to do so while avoiding spoilers.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Detroit: Become Human&lt;/em&gt; is a story-heavy adventure game developed by Quantic Dream, the studio I knew best as the creators of &lt;em&gt;Heavy Rain&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The story takes place in a future where androids are commonplace and indistinguishable from humans aside from a computer chip placed on their temple. Predictably, the androids are mistreated and repressed by humans, and you eventually find yourself in the middle of a robot uprising.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What staying home has been like for me so far</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-staying-home-has-been-like-for-me-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-staying-home-has-been-like-for-me-so-far/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;things-that-changed&#34;&gt;Things that changed&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I have more time in the morning to do things around the house instead of commuting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Remote meetings are a little harder than in-person meetings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I write daily reports about my work progress, equally to show my teammates that I’m staying on track, and to keep myself on track&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We watch the news a lot more&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I don’t wear socks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Pushing my social life online has lead to me talking to friends more than before&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;things-that-didnt-change&#34;&gt;Things that didn’t change&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Waking up in the morning is hard&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Work hours are mostly the same, or a little longer from the lack of a commute&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;There is still a lot of work to do and I am busy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I still shave and brush my teeth and shower&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I get dressed in the morning&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We get groceries delivered once a week&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The world is stressful, but being able to stay at home is a blessing so total stress balances out&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The dog doesn’t seem to care that I’m around&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape Up - How Basecamp does Product Development</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/shape-up-how-basecamp-does-product-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/shape-up-how-basecamp-does-product-development/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://basecamp.com/shapeup&#34;&gt;Shape Up&lt;/a&gt; is an amazing new web-book by Basecamp that details the process they use to define, build, and ship their products. It has great insights, but I especially appreciated how many of the ideas presented just make a lot of sense. I often nodded along in agreement and recognized concepts that we share in our team. The framework is battle-tested and realistic, and there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to integrate some new ideas into our existing workflow without having to reorganize how we think about everything to fit a new metaphor.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ōkunoshima - The Island of Bunnies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/okunoshima---the-island-of-bunnies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/okunoshima---the-island-of-bunnies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/okunoshima/okunoshima24.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Located east of Hiroshima in the Seto Inland Sea, Ōkunoshima (大久野島) is a small island home to over 700 rabbits. The rabbits are wild but friendly, and tourists arrive every day with bags full of food and treats. The island was relatively unknown in Japan until recently when its populality among foreign visitors brought it into the spotlight.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- more --&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-dark-history&#34;&gt;A Dark History&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ōkunoshima today is a paradise of cuteness, but its origins are sinister. Chosen for its remote location, it contained secret facilities used to develop and produce poison gas for chemical weapons. The island was erased from maps at the time to hide its existence. The ruins of these facilities still exist, covered by moss and providing a grim backdrop for those who choose to explore the island.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding CSS Support for Dark Mode</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/adding-css-support-for-dark-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/adding-css-support-for-dark-mode/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/darkmode.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;macOS Mojave added a system-wide Dark Mode, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t do much if all of the websites you see are still bright white. To address this, there is a new CSS media query &lt;code&gt;prefers-color-scheme&lt;/code&gt; that can detect Dark Mode and change styles accordingly. There are three possible values: &lt;code&gt;no-preference&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;light&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;dark&lt;/code&gt;. You can read more in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://drafts.csswg.org/mediaqueries-5/#prefers-color-scheme&#34;&gt;W3C specification&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This new option &lt;a href=&#34;https://caniuse.com/#feat=prefers-color-scheme&#34;&gt;looks to be supported&lt;/a&gt; in Safari 12.1 and Firefox 67. As of this writing both of these have not been released officially, but you can try it out in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://developer.apple.com/safari/technology-preview/&#34;&gt;Safari Technology Preview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Image of a Black Hole</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-image-of-a-black-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-image-of-a-black-hole/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/blackhole.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Credit: Event Horizon Telescope collaboration et al.&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the first time ever, scientists have captured &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nsf.gov/news/news_summ.jsp?cntn_id=298276&#34;&gt;an image of a black hole&lt;/a&gt;. The black hole chosen is a supermassive black hole at the center of the Messier 87 galaxy, 55 million light-years away from Earth. This is huge news, since before this we only had theoretical proofs of black holes with no direct evidence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A black hole technically doesn&amp;rsquo;t look like anything since it emits no light, so I understand this to be a capture of light that came very close to the black hole. It appears in a very distinct way that confirms the presence of a black hole.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Lighting in the Office</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/natural-lighting-in-the-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/natural-lighting-in-the-office/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve come to learn that I really enjoy working in environments with only natural lighting. At my job, I work in a large open room with about 50 people. Many of them are artists who need to minimize the glare on their screens, so the great big windows covering the walls of our room are always covered with blinds, and we instead have fluorescent lights turned on (these do cause glare too, but at least they are more predictable so people can tilt their screens to minimize it).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Colors from Post Titles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/adding-color-to-posts-automatically/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/adding-color-to-posts-automatically/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This blog has an intentionally simple design, but lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking that it needs more color. A lot of the posts don&amp;rsquo;t have images and are just text, so large areas of the page are black and white with nothing visually interesting. That said, trying to include an image with every post is a pain. I would probably spend more time browsing stock images than actually writing the posts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Maker&#39;s Schedule - A Ten Year Retrospective</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-makers-schedule-a-ten-year-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-makers-schedule-a-ten-year-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;10 years ago, I was fresh out of college and encountered &lt;a href=&#34;http://paulgraham.com/makersschedule.html&#34;&gt;Paul Graham&amp;rsquo;s essay&lt;/a&gt; about the maker&amp;rsquo;s schedule, and wrote &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/programmers-stop-whining-be-productive&#34;&gt;a response&lt;/a&gt; disagreeing with the spirit of the article. While I knew and understood that programmers could be much more productive in one 10 hour chunk than in five 2 hour chunks, I felt like rearranging a business&amp;rsquo;s operations based on these preferences was going overboard. The typical programmer as described seemed undisciplined, and I wrote that programmers needed to find ways to work around distractions, which are simply a fact of life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mental Training, and Learning to Swim</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mental-training-and-learning-to-swim/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mental-training-and-learning-to-swim/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;During my last year at university, I decided to learn to swim. I was reasonably confident in my ability to stay afloat in deep water and not die, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t what you could call swimming. Luckily, two of my close friends were excellent swimmers and they agreed to work with me in the mornings before class.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As an aside, I did take swimming lessons on and off for a few years when I was a kid, but apparently I retained nothing from those classes. Maybe I was just a terrible swimmer the entire time? Possibly related, &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/i-grew-up-in-high-school&#34;&gt;I have very few memories from my elementary and middle school years&lt;/a&gt;, so I have a suspicion that I didn&amp;rsquo;t do a whole lot of thinking when I was a kid. In any case, I was essentially a total beginner to swimming when we started. I knew that you kicked your legs and paddled with your arms to go forward, but that was about it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Cut of the Dead (カメラを止めるな！）</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/one-cut-of-the-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/one-cut-of-the-dead/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://kametome.net/index.html&#34;&gt;One Cut of the Dead (カメラを止めるな！)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is a low budget Japanese zombie movie that became hugely popular here. I just watched it over the weekend and it was wonderful. The writing is very funny and very clever, and when it was over I found myself immediately wanting to watch it a second time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/One_Cut_of_the_Dead&#34;&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One Cut of the Dead was made for 3 million Japanese Yen (approximately $25,000 in US Dollars at the time) with a cast of unknown actors. It was made in eight days after director Shinichiro Ueda participated in workshops for actors and filmmakers at the Enbu Seminar drama school in Tokyo&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spaghetti Carbonara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/spaghetti-carbonara/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/spaghetti-carbonara/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For a long time I thought I didn&amp;rsquo;t like carbonara because the few I tried were too creamy and eggy. Recently I gave it another try because the picture in the menu looked delicious. It was excellent, and I decided I wanted to learn how to make it myself. I needed some practice before I felt comfortable with the timings, but overall it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty simple recipe that wasn&amp;rsquo;t hard to learn.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucid Dreaming</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lucid-dreaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lucid-dreaming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was consistently able to have lucid dreams when I was in high school. Partway through a dream, I would realize that I was dreaming and could then control the rest of the dream to a small extent. As I&amp;rsquo;ve grown older though, this has become less and less common. Maybe age has changed something about my brain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Naturally, I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in lucid dreaming and have read a lot about it. &lt;a href=&#34;https://tim.blog/2009/09/21/how-to-lucid-dream/&#34;&gt;Tim Ferriss has a fascinating beginner&amp;rsquo;s guide on his blog&lt;/a&gt;. Different people seem to have different approaches and theories, so I thought I would write about my own experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Basic Income</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/universal-basic-income/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/universal-basic-income/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I wonder sometimes about what a better society than ours would be. What should our goals be as we try to improve?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As our society improves and we get more efficient, I like to imagine a future where we don&amp;rsquo;t have to work as much. That seems like a nice thing to aim for. Universal basic income (UBI) seems like one possible solution. If we could afford to give everybody a fixed minimal income, people could work less and still have a basic amount of wealth needed to survive. But I&amp;rsquo;m not yet convinced whether UBI is the correct answer to describe an ideal future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Value Promise of Subscription Games</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-value-promise-of-subscription-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-value-promise-of-subscription-games/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had been playing World of Warcraft on and off for about 10 years, but I decided to stop playing again about a year ago. I quit because of a series of changes that were made to the game, and it motivated me to think about why I reacted that way as a paying customer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A series of recent changes made to WoW were designed to motivate players to play by ensuring they always gain something and grow a little every time they play. Unfortunately, a side effect of these changes was an increased pressure to spend many hours playing. This made me feel like my limited time spent in the game was less valuable, and is what ultimately led to me quitting the game.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Cook Popcorn in a Pan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-cook-popcorn-in-a-pan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-cook-popcorn-in-a-pan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The best way to cook popcorn in a pan. The secret is to heat up the kernels evenly in hot oil first, before heating them over a flame to pop them quickly all at once.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Coat the bottom of a pan with a small amount of oil and place over medium heat.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Put three popcorn kernels in the pan and wait for all three to pop.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Put the rest of the kernels in the pan, cover with a lid, and &lt;strong&gt;remove from the heat&lt;/strong&gt; for 30 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;This heats the kernels evenly, getting them all ready to pop together.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Return the pan to the heat, where the popcorn should start popping right away.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It helps to keep the lid ajar and shake the pan occasionally to keep the popcorn dry.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Once the popping slows to a few seconds between pops, pour the popcorn into a bowl.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add salt to taste.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/popcorn.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Photo by Keegan Evans from Pexels&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Idea: PvP Pac-Man</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pvp-pacman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pvp-pacman/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;concept&#34;&gt;Concept&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Play Pac-Man online against other players. 1 player plays as Pac-Man and 4 other players play as the ghosts. Pac-Man&amp;rsquo;s goal is to collect as many dots as possible, and the ghosts&amp;rsquo; goal is to work together to catch Pac-Man. Players receive points at the end of the round based on performance, and roles are rotated for the next round.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;gameplay&#34;&gt;Gameplay&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In terms of strategy, the ghosts will need to work together in order to win. Pac-Man will move faster than the ghosts, so the ghosts&amp;rsquo; main strategy will be to trap Pac-Man in a corner. To encourage teamwork, all ghosts will receive the same amount of points at the end of round regardless of who actually caught Pac-Man.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Value of Blockchain Platforms</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/blockchain-platforms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 21:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/blockchain-platforms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking a lot recently about what benefits there are to building a new product on a blockchain. Blockchains allow an app to be decentralized, and the biggest value they bring is a solid way to handle trust and consensus in an environment with no central authority. I was having a hard time thinking of products that would really benefit from being decentralized, but I came across an idea about decentralized platforms that makes a very strong case for using blockchains.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Is No Longer a Communication Platform</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/facebook-is-no-longer-a-communication-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 19:53:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/facebook-is-no-longer-a-communication-platform/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I started using Facebook in 2005, it was exclusive to college students and was by far the best way to communicate with my classmates. It was the first time I could learn what my friends were up to without asking each one individually. Everything I wanted to know about my friends was in one easily accessible place.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All recent updates were shown as one long list, but Facebook eventually introduced the News Feed. This was an effort to filter everyone&amp;rsquo;s updates to show just the most important ones. Facebook made educated guesses about whose updates were most important to you and hid the ones you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t care about. I think they also kept an option to see all updates in chronological order if you didn&amp;rsquo;t want to miss out on anything.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Video Games Still For Kids?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/are-games-still-for-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 17:47:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/are-games-still-for-kids/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I grew up in the 90s, and back then video games were made for kids. Toys were for kids, and video games were just the newest, most exciting toys around.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But as my generation grew up, we never really stopped playing games. As we became adults, the game companies kept making games for us, and games shifted to targeting an older audience. It makes sense that these would be successful since adults have more money to spend on games than kids do. Video games became a form of entertainment just like movies, and they started using serious storylines and graphic violence in the same ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s AlphaZero Destroys Stockfish In 100-Game Match</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/google-s-alphazero-destroys-stockfish-in-100-game-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 22:58:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/google-s-alphazero-destroys-stockfish-in-100-game-match/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Google&amp;rsquo;s AlphaZero program is a machine that plays chess, and it has managed to quickly become the strongest chess AI in the world by implementing machine learning techniques. While existing chess AIs have mostly been massive dictionaries of moves that are put together by humans, AlphaZero learned chess entirely on its own with minimal human input.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I understand it, the hardest part of creating an AI that solves problems like chess is finding some way to calculate if you&amp;rsquo;re winning or not. If that were easy to do, the program could just look at all of its possible moves (which is not very many for a computer) and see which one would leave it winning by more. The trouble is that it&amp;rsquo;s very hard to tell if you&amp;rsquo;re winning. You might need to consider all possible outcomes many moves in advance, which quickly becomes too many to calculate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay to Win</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pay-to-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 18:59:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pay-to-win/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mobile games can make a crazy amount of money. &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Puzzle_%26_Dragons&#34;&gt;Puzzles and Dragons&lt;/a&gt; at its peak was said to be earning &lt;em&gt;$100 million per month&lt;/em&gt;! Why do people spend so much?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mobile games are generally much more simple than traditional video games, so they can&amp;rsquo;t provide the same rich experiences as traditional video games. Instead, they engage their core users by providing a satisfying experience of winning, especially against other players. Since people often play mobile games in their spare time, money is used as a shortcut to win quickly and efficiently. The entire game&amp;rsquo;s structure is built around creating an environment to support people who are willing to pay large amounts of money in order to win.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let’s stop the hate</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lets-stop-the-hate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 18:44:38 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lets-stop-the-hate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m a supporter of LGBT rights. I&#39;m generally not too vocal about it, but with recent events culminating in the Orlando mass shootings, I had to say something.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve been thinking a lot about the LGBT rights movement recently. Hopefully this effort can be another step forward following the Civil Rights Movement, as we work towards equal rights and treatment for all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Civil Rights Act made it illegal to discriminate based on race, color, religion, sex, or national origin. Setting religion aside for a moment, the rest are distinctions that generally lead to noticeable physical differences. The ease of identification is probably one factor that helped the prejudice spread so much, and led to institutional disenfranchisement as well as terrible acts of discrimination and violence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pluto - Closest Approach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pluto-closest-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 11:41:17 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pluto-closest-approach/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote class=&#34;twitter-tweet&#34; data-lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&lt;p lang=&#34;en&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Hello &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/hashtag/Pluto?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;#Pluto&lt;/a&gt;! We’re at closest approach. Congrats to all! Follow our story &amp;amp; view new images using &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/hashtag/PlutoFlyby?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;#PlutoFlyby&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;http://t.co/8JVlJrcUkY&#34;&gt;pic.twitter.com/8JVlJrcUkY&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; NASA New Horizons (@NASANewHorizons) &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/NASANewHorizons/status/620923200621412352?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;July 14, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;script async src=&#34;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And here is the best picture we had previously, taken by Hubble. Pretty amazing stuff&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/pluto-hubble-01.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Pluto&#34; width=&#34;400px&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ゲームの空間認識と今後の進化</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/%E3%82%B2%E3%83%BC%E3%83%A0%E3%81%AE%E7%A9%BA%E9%96%93%E8%AA%8D%E8%AD%98%E3%81%A8%E4%BB%8A%E5%BE%8C%E3%81%AE%E9%80%B2%E5%8C%96/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 13:59:55 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/%E3%82%B2%E3%83%BC%E3%83%A0%E3%81%AE%E7%A9%BA%E9%96%93%E8%AA%8D%E8%AD%98%E3%81%A8%E4%BB%8A%E5%BE%8C%E3%81%AE%E9%80%B2%E5%8C%96/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;チームラボの猪子氏がTEDxFukuokaで紹介した、日本と西洋での空間認識の違いについての話がとてもおもしろかったので紹介。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://logmi.jp/23783&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;マリオはなぜ世界でヒットしたのか？　チームラボ・猪子氏が語る、日本的空間認識とクリエイティビティの関係性&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;プレゼンテーションの内容を省略すると、&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;西洋の空間認識だと、パースペクティブを意識する。&#xA;よって、絵の登場人物になりきると視点が変わって絵の全体を意識しなくなる。絵の全体の意識が変わる、と言う方が適切なのかもしれない。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;日本の空間認識だと、レイヤーで物を見て、重ねて表現する。&#xA;絵の登場人物になりきっても、絵の認識が変わらず、絵の全体を意識し続ける。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;これが、日本が産んだマリオやドラクエみたいなプラットフォーマーや、トップダウンRPGなどの表現を作ったゲームの原点で、アメリカではもっと登場人物の視点で遊ぶFPSなどが流行りやすい。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;とのこと。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ハードのスペックで3Dの表現ができなかったことも大きい、と想像しつつも、とても興味深い話。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oculus Rift 用に開発中の&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wired.com/2014/06/oculus-luckys-tale/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Lucky’s Tale&lt;/a&gt;の話を思い出した。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lucky&amp;rsquo;s TaleはVR機能を活かした3Dのプラットフォーマーなのだが、自分が主人公になりきるわけではない。キャラクターの視点と自分の視点は完全に別で、自分が3Dの世界の中で、主人公の隣に居るという見せ方。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;開発者曰く、たくさんの案をとにかく作りまくっているうちに偶然出来上がったものだったが、少し遊んでみると体験の斬新さに全員が驚いた、とのこと。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上の話に合わせると、VRなのでパースペクティブで入り込むのはほぼ必須として、それでもマリオのようにキャラと空間の全体の絵を意識し続けれるような、全く新しい形になっているような気がする。おそらく実際遊んでみないと体験を想像できないと思うので、リリースが楽しみだ。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missingno. in Pokemon Fusion</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/missingno-in-pokemon-fusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2014 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/missingno-in-pokemon-fusion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve made a small update to the &lt;a href=&#34;http://pokemon.alexonsager.net&#34;&gt;Pokemon Fusion&lt;/a&gt; site, and added Missingno. as a hidden pokemon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was inspired by the incredible Mewtwo x Missingno. fusion artwork that was posted by StarvingStudents on his &lt;a href=&#34;http://starvingstudents.deviantart.com/art/Mewssingno-472862222&#34;&gt;deviantART page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Missingno. appears whenever there is an invalid ID in the URL, so acts as a fun 404 page. You can try it out &lt;a href=&#34;http://pokemon.alexonsager.net/25/0&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/assets/images/pikassingno.png&#34; alt=&#34;Pikassingno.&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The glich images were generated with ImageMagick (the Rmagick ruby gem in particular), using the spread function to displace pixels by a certain amount. In this case, I also shrunk the image first to exaggerate the pixelation, and it brought it back to normal size afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Censoring Chinese Scammers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/censoring-chinese-scammers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 14:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/censoring-chinese-scammers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Q: What do you do when you&amp;rsquo;re being scammed by a Chinese scam artist?&#xA;A: Use their country&amp;rsquo;s internet censorship against them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LINE, the hugely popular Japanese messaging app, has been seeing a recent surge in scamming activity. In the most common scenario, the scam artist will gain access to a user&amp;rsquo;s account and message their friends, asking them to purchase online gift cards and send the serial number. Many people were targeted by this scam, and it received some mainstream media attention.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating Fun</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 23:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-fun/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My long-standing goal, in both work and personal life, is to create &amp;ldquo;fun&amp;rdquo;. I currently make games for a living, so I&amp;rsquo;ll be focusing on games for this post.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-fun&#34;&gt;What is Fun?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Games like &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flappy_Bird&#34;&gt;Flappy Bird&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://gabrielecirulli.github.io/2048/&#34;&gt;2048&lt;/a&gt; show that as long as you have one crucial element that provides fun, even the simplest of games can be a huge hit. And in fact, for games like these it is necessary that they be the simplest of games, with no other elements distracting from that core nugget of fun.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「面白い」を創る</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-fun-jp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 23:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-fun-jp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;仕事でも、プライベートでも、自分の昔からの目標は「面白い」を創ること。&#xA;ゲームを創る職についているので、今回はゲームの話が中心となる。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;面白いとは&#34;&gt;「面白い」とは？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flappy_Bird&#34;&gt;Flappy Bird&lt;/a&gt;や&lt;a href=&#34;http://gabrielecirulli.github.io/2048/&#34;&gt;2048&lt;/a&gt;のようなゲームが見せてくれたように、&#xA;根本的な面白い要素さえあれば、どんなシンプルなゲームでも大ヒットする可能性がある。&#xA;むしろ、これらのゲームは最もシンプルであることが必須で、根本の面白さの邪魔をする要素がない、というのも成功の要因だと言える。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://asherv.com/threes/&#34;&gt;Threes&lt;/a&gt;の製作者は、凄まじい量のブレストと改善を行った上でゲームをリリースした。&#xA;その途中で、いずれ2048としてリリースされるゲームシステムを検討したが、彼らの思う「良いゲーム」の定義に当てはまらなく、ボツにされた。&#xA;2048のシステムだと、一つの角に寄せて操作すると簡単に高得点が出せるので、それが「正しい」遊び方になってしまう。&#xA;おそらく、彼らはゲームとしての深みを重視して、それがゲームの良さを損なうと考え、別のシステムを創った。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;結果としては、ゲームの「良さ」を損なうと疑われた要素はゲームの「面白さ」につながり、単純な方のシステムを適用した2048が全世界で大ヒットした。&#xA;実際Threesのゲームとしてのクオリティーはかなり高く評価されていて、Threesを否定するわけではない。&#xA;ただ、いくら客観的に見てThreesが良いゲームであっても、「2048の方が面白い」と思った人の方が多かった。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;面白いを探す&#34;&gt;「面白い」を探す&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;残念なことに、「面白い」は捕えにくい。一生懸命探せば探すほど、見つからない。&#xA;それを見つけるにはとてもクリエイティブな思考が必要で、たまたま得た発想が案外、有益をもたらすことが多い。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自分が新しい物を創る時、なにが面白くなりそうかを考えることに必ずなる。&#xA;ただ、これがうまく行くとは限らず、面白い発想が出ない悪循環にもなり得る。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;万人の受けを予想しようとすると、現在万人受けしている物を参考にせざるを得ない。&#xA;考え始める前から、すでに枠の中に入ってしまっているわけだ。&#xA;プロセスはおそらく以下のようになる：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;人気がある物を見る&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;なぜそれが面白いかを分析する&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;その面白さを、新しい形で再現する&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;「新しい形」のところで近道をしている人がありふれたパクリゲームを作ることになるわけだが、&#xA;真面目に新しく考えようとしても、既存の物から思考がスタートしている時点で、創れる物の幅が狭くなってしまう。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;面白いを発見する&#34;&gt;「面白い」を発見する&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;プロセスはこうあるべきだ：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;新しい発想を得る&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;それを面白くする方法を考える&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;その面白さに集中して、余計な要素を無くす&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;奇跡的に、&lt;a href=&#34;http://pokemon.alexonsager.net&#34;&gt;ポケモンフュージョン&lt;/a&gt;はこれを果たしていると思う。&#xA;ある日その単純な発想が頭に浮かんで、そこに見つけた面白さはシンプルなサイトでも伝わる物だった。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;新しい発想を得ることは簡単ではなく、自分ももっと簡単にする方法を探している。&#xA;一番大事なことは、自分が興味のあるものを推し進めることだと思う。&#xA;「興味深い」の先には必ず「面白い」があると考えていて、そこに行き着くためには自らの熱意が必要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;その先で「面白い」を見つけることができたら、多分それは自分しか見つけることが出来なかった新しい「面白い」であろう。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco Is Dead. Long Live San Francisco</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/san-francisco-is-dead-long-live-san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/san-francisco-is-dead-long-live-san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.modernluxury.com/san-francisco/story/san-francisco-dead-long-live-san-francisco&#34;&gt;Gary Kamiya&lt;/a&gt; in San Francisco Magazine, talking about the many factors and consequences of San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(I)f present trends continue, the city could soon become a moated citadel of info-money, accessible only to venture capitalists, Twitter engineers, and the creators of hookup apps.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This prospect worries me. As someone who loves San Francisco’s maverick tradition and its class and ethnic diversity (I celebrated both in a book I wrote last year called Cool Gray City of Love), I find the idea that my beloved town is on the verge of becoming another Manhattan—a picturesque but increasingly expensive, homogeneous, and sterile burg—distressing, to put it mildly.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And yet, the political, cultural, and class war that has erupted over what is happening to San Francisco—call it the Change—strikes me as wrongheaded to the point of surreality.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I’m all for rushing the barricades when there’s an enemy to fight and a battle that can be won. I’ve engaged in my share of such battles. But it’s time to reckon with reality: There is no enemy here. Or if there is, it’s an enemy that won’t be defeated. What has hit San Francisco in the last couple of years can be summed up in one word: capitalism. And that is a tsunami that no seawall can keep out.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>夜桜</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/yozakura/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/yozakura/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/yozakura.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/yozakura_s.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;夜桜&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone 5 Wallpaper - Stormtrooper Prism</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/iphone-5-wallpaper-stormtrooper-prism/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 13:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/iphone-5-wallpaper-stormtrooper-prism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/assets/images/stormtrooper.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/stormtrooper_s.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Stormtrooper Prism&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please let me know if you know the source of this image.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;UPDATE: Artwork by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.liambrazier.com/&#34;&gt;Liam Brazier&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love is Overdrive</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/love-is-overdrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/love-is-overdrive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ラブ･イズ・オーバーっていう、超有名な曲があって、&#xA;ラブ･イズ・オーバーは、愛が終わったって意味やけど&#xA;愛が終わっただけでは寂しいんで&#xA;ラブ・イズ・オーバーでドライブしたら&#xA;ラブ・イズ・オーバー・ドライブ&#xA;オーバードライブしてたら愛は全開に変わった&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;ヤバオカムーブメンツ・中村隆太&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sexisim on the Red Carpet</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sexisim-on-the-red-carpet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sexisim-on-the-red-carpet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://mattsgifs.com/post/73774946424&#34;&gt;During an E! interview at a red carpet ceremony&lt;/a&gt;, the camera operator takes a sweeping toe-to-head shot of Cate Blanchett, when she crouches down to ask, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Do you do that to the guys?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; The internet explodes with opinion, and more fuel is added to the increasing fight against the objectification of women in media.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The way I see it, the camera operator was just doing their job. Red carpet ceremonies are events focused on fashion, and Cate Blanchett was wearing a very nice gown that should be seen in its entirety. No, most male guests would not have received the same treatment, because most male guests would be wearing suits or tuxedos and everybody knows what black pants look like.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Replace Text in File - OSX Service</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/replace-text-in-file-osx-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 20:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/replace-text-in-file-osx-service/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A quick Mac OSX service that will search and replace all given strings in a text file, and save the modified content as a new file. It&amp;rsquo;s not &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; much faster than just opening it in a text editor, but it was a fun way to learn how sed works.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://images.alexonsager.net/blog/Replace_Text.zip&#34;&gt;Download the script here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It just runs a simple AppleScript that prompts for the query strings and new filename, and then runs sed through the shell to do the string replacements.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminal Theme</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/terminal-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 15:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/terminal-theme/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/terminal.png&#34; alt=&#34;New Terminal setup&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can download the theme &lt;a href=&#34;http://images.alexonsager.net/downloads/Base16.terminal.zip&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Colors were taken from the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/chriskempson/base16-textmate&#34;&gt;Base16 TextMate theme&lt;/a&gt;, and the font is &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/fonts/specimen/Source+Code+Pro&#34;&gt;Source Code Pro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://backup.noiseandheat.com/blog/2011/12/os-x-lion-terminal-colours/&#34;&gt;These&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://osxdaily.com/2013/02/05/improve-terminal-appearance-mac-os-x/&#34;&gt;sites&lt;/a&gt; describe how to get your Terminal to start showing colors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargekey Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chargekey-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2014 20:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chargekey-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently received a review unit of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hellonomad.com/products/chargekey-iphone5&#34;&gt;Chargekey&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s essentially a key-sized USB to Lightning cable that you will can have available on your keychain (They also make a Micro-USB version to fit your Android phone). I don&amp;rsquo;t do too much wandering around during the day, but I hadn&amp;rsquo;t bought a second cable for charging my phone while at work so I was more than happy to start making daily use of this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rake task to backup MySQL to Amazon S3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/rake-task-to-backup-mysql-to-amazon-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 01:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/rake-task-to-backup-mysql-to-amazon-s3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A simple rake task to dump the contents of a MySQL database and save it to an Amazon S3 bucket. Use together with &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/javan/whenever&#34;&gt;whenever&lt;/a&gt; to automate it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-ruby&#34; data-lang=&#34;ruby&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;namespace &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;:backup&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;do&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  task &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;:nightly&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;do&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    timestamp &lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;Time&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;now&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;strftime(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;%Y-%m-%d_%H-%M-%S&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;)&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    backup_file &lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;tmp/backups/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;timestamp&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;_dump.sql.gz&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;`mkdir -p tmp/backups`&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;`mysqldump -u root {DATABASE_NAME} | gzip -c &amp;gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;backup_file&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;`&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    send_to_s3 backup_file&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;send_to_s3&lt;/span&gt;(file_path)&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    bucket &lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;{BUCKET_NAME}&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    file_name &lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;File&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;basename(file_path)&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;AWS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;S3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;DEFAULT_HOST&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;replace &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;AWS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;S3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;Base&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;establish_connection!(&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;      &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;:access_key_id&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;{KEY}&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;,&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;      &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;:secret_access_key&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;{SECRET}&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;)&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;AWS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;S3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;S3Object&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;store(&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;      &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;backups/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;file_name&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;,&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;      &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;File&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;open(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;file_path&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;),&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;      bucket)&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Fusion: Behind the Scenes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/behind-the-scenes-pokemon-fusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2013 00:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/behind-the-scenes-pokemon-fusion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting a few questions about the script used to generate the &lt;a href=&#34;http://pokemon.alexonsager.net&#34;&gt;Pokemon Fusion&lt;/a&gt; sprites, so I thought I would write a quick blog post to describe the process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The inspiration of the website was the idea that it should be possible to automate the process of combining pokemon sprites, and each image is automatically generated by a computer script. Some of the results are less impressive than others, but I think that it adds to the fun and makes it that much more satisfying when you come across ones that work really well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save to Pocket - OSX Service</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/save-to-pocket-osx-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 00:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/save-to-pocket-osx-service/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick Mac OSX service that will allow you to save any link to Pocket by right-clicking it. It will work from within basically any app that lets you right-click text. Prerequisite is that you have the Pocket OSX app installed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://images.alexonsager.net/downloads/SavetoPocket.zip&#34;&gt;Download the script here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After downloading, unzip and place the file in ~/Library/Services (or create the folder first if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist already)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After doing so, you should be able to simply highlight a link and right-click it to see the &amp;ldquo;Save to Pocket&amp;rdquo; option. (You might find it under a &amp;ldquo;Services&amp;rdquo; category)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on &#34;Sourcecode&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/thoughts-on-sourcecode/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/thoughts-on-sourcecode/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve finally come to terms with the movie &lt;em&gt;Sourcecode&lt;/em&gt;. But at first, I hated it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The premise is that scientists have built a machine that can:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;extract remnants of memory from a person&amp;rsquo;s brain and&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;allow a 2nd person&amp;rsquo;s consciousness to then enter those memories and experience them firsthand.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They then use this machine to have someone enter the memory of a person present at a train bombing, so that he can find the culprit and stop the next crime.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Crossword Puzzle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/amazing-crossword-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/amazing-crossword-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/crossword.gif&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The New York Times crossword puzzle the day before the 1996 presidential election.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The relevant clues:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;across&#34;&gt;Across&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;17&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Forecast&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lead story in tomorrow’s newspaper (!), with 43-Across&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Title for 39-Across next year&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;down&#34;&gt;Down&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;23&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sewing shop purchase&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Short writings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Trumpet&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Black Halloween animal&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;French 101 word&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Provider of support, for short&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Much-debated polital inits.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pray for Japan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pray-for-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pray-for-japan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After the 3/11 earthquake, #prayforjapan was a hashtag used for people around the world to send messages of encouragement to Japan. &lt;a href=&#34;http://prayforjapan.jp/&#34;&gt;prayforjapan.jp&lt;/a&gt; is a site that is collecting heartwarming tweets from Japanese users, as well as messages from outside the country.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I got emotional after reading just a few of these messages. The earthquake was a terrible tragedy, but amidst all of that I feel admiration for the spirit of the Japanese people. Messages like this show that people have really come together to help one another, and it give me great hope for the country’s recovery.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Grew Up in High School</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/i-grew-up-in-high-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/i-grew-up-in-high-school/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I might even say that I didn’t grow up in any meaningful way before I started high school.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve always felt like I have very limited memories of middle school and elementary school. The problem, as I realized recently, isn’t that I have few memories. Rather, it is that my memories don’t seem to include my thoughts – what I wondered, what I thought about, and how I felt about certain things. When probing my memories I get plenty of clear images, but I can’t help but feel like an observer; I can see my past-self doing things and reacting to events, but I have no idea what that child was thinking. I mean, I can guess. I’m sure I’d be pretty good at guessing, since I know the kid well, but it’s strange that this isn’t part of the memory.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Incredible Network of Children</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-incredible-network-of-children/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-incredible-network-of-children/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When we were kids, we didn’t use online forums, message boards, or FAQs. Yet somehow, every single child knew that if your videogame wasn’t working, you just needed to blow in the cartridge. And it’s not like anybody documented Red Rover or Wall Ball or Groundies/Lava Monster. Kids just talked to each other and figured it out.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Steps to an Effective Tech Team</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/five-steps-to-an-effective-tech-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/five-steps-to-an-effective-tech-team/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently experienced two of the most informative and useful meetings of my life. Lloyd Taylor, the former VP of Technical Operations at LinkedIn, and Olana Khan, the former COO of Kiva, graciously donated their time to speak to us about how to organize our technology goals. We had been in the process of formalizing our thoughts for an upcoming board meeting, but their expert feedback allowed us to cement in some much-needed structure. In addition, we also were given invaluable advice about how to lead an effective technology team in general.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Cups of Tea</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/three-cups-of-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/three-cups-of-tea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Three Cups of Tea&lt;/em&gt; is the most inspiring book I have ever read.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is the true story following Greg Mortenson, a mountaineer who attempts to climb K2. On his way down, he stumbles into a tiny village in Pakistan and vows to return one day to build a school for the children there. He is successful, and is urged by others to continue building schools for underprivileged children across Pakistan. His story is remarkable, and the amount of impact he has managed to bring as one man with audacious goals is astounding.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gogol Bordello – Oakland 2009</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/gogol-bordello-oakland-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/gogol-bordello-oakland-2009/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently saw Gogol Bordello perform live for the second time. The first was a year (two years?) ago in San Francisco, and it was the wildest, most exhilarating event I have ever attended. Many concerts have &amp;ldquo;that one song,&amp;rdquo; that brings the entire audience together in a fever of enthusiasm to focus entirely on the music and the performance. Gogol Bordello managed to maintain this state for the entire 2 hour show. The rush of being in a huge crowd of people screaming in unison and immersed in the moment, led by the gods of gypsy punk, was indescribable. But enough about last year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook and Non-Profits: Revolutionizing with Samasource</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/facebook-and-non-profits-revolutionizing-with-samasource/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/facebook-and-non-profits-revolutionizing-with-samasource/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Originally posted on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://fbfund.com/facebook-and-non-profits-revolutionizing-with-samasource/&#34;&gt;fbFund blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While a Stanford undergrad, I began my online career with gleeful audacity. The Monday after Facebook Platform launched, my friend and I released Facebook&amp;rsquo;s original Graffiti application. We were unexperienced and had no viral component, so we soon lost the battle to Mark Kantor et al.&amp;rsquo;s version. But Graffiti gave us excitement and hunger. The following fall we enrolled in Stanford&amp;rsquo;s course on Facebook applications, using the opportunity to develop Send Hotness. This time, we nailed the virality. A few advertising payouts later, we were the proud owners of two companies. Doped up on adrenaline, we loved every minute. I stepped down eventually once I remembered that I had schoolwork to do, but I felt sure that this was my path.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programmers: Stop Whining, Be Productive</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/programmers-stop-whining-be-productive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/programmers-stop-whining-be-productive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[!NOTE] Update 2019&#xA;10 years later, I have posted a reflection on this piece [[the-maker&amp;rsquo;s-schedule-a-ten-year-retrospective | here]].&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was pointed to &lt;a href=&#34;http://paulgraham.com/makersschedule.html&#34;&gt;Paul Graham’s post&lt;/a&gt; about programmers running on a separate schedule than other people. Programmers run on the &amp;ldquo;maker’s schedule&amp;rdquo; and prefer to work in large chunks of time, with units of at least half a day. Others, particularly their bosses, operate on the &amp;ldquo;manager’s schedule&amp;rdquo; and have things defined into hour-long chunks. Interactions between the two typically cause friction:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/extremely-loud-and-incredibly-close/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/extremely-loud-and-incredibly-close/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazingly imaginative&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the story of Oskar Schell, a young boy who is on a quest around New York City, attempting to solve a mystery left in the wake of his father’s death in the 9/11 attacks. The story is told in the form of narratives, letters, and journal entries from the perspective of three individuals, and their interwoven stories are revealed expertly in parallel. The book works as a scrapbook, with the reader discovering elements from the story appearing on the pages, as though they had been pasted in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Elegance of the Hedgehog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-elegance-of-the-hedgehog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-elegance-of-the-hedgehog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Profoundly moving&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By Muriel Barbery, this novel is the story of two hyper-intelligent individuals living among Paris’ high society: Renée Michel, the concierge of the apartment building, and Paloma Josse, the shockingly perceptive 12-year-old. They seem to embody everything that the privileged elite should be but isn’t; the juxtaposition of their wisdom and class against the frivolous and shallow natures of those around them constantly lashes out at the empty finicking of the bourgeois lifestyles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samasource Selected for fbFund REV</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/samasource-selected-for-fbfund-rev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/samasource-selected-for-fbfund-rev/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hooray! Along with 18 companies and one other non-profit, &lt;strong&gt;Samasource was chosen to participate in fbFund’s incubator program this summer&lt;/strong&gt;. Check out the full list of winners on &lt;a href=&#34;http://venturebeat.com/2009/05/28/fbfund-17-companies-and-2-nonprofits-win-head-to-palo-alto/&#34;&gt;VentureBeat&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.insidefacebook.com/2009/05/28/facebook-announces-19-2009-fbfund-winners/&#34;&gt;InsideFacebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What this means is that we’ll have Palo Alto office space, lots of media attention, an official Facebook seal of approval, and possibly free lunches &lt;em&gt;/crossfingers&lt;/em&gt;. The catch?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Due to the way fbFund is structured, the non-profit startups cannot receive funding (&lt;a href=&#34;http://developers.facebook.com/news.php?blog=1&amp;amp;story=249&#34;&gt;Facebook dev blog&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meals as a Social Activity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/meals-as-a-social-activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/meals-as-a-social-activity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I ate dinner alone. I think there is nothing wrong with that, but you just don’t see people alone in restaurants all that often (Aren’t you going to be bored? Do you want a magazine or something?). Eating meals, in most cultures everywhere, is regarded as a social activity. I would like to explore why, and have a few hypotheses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Everybody has to do it&lt;/strong&gt;. Three times a day, nearly everybody will eat food at roughly the same time. People share this activity, and so it makes sense for that time to be designated for social interaction. If everybody had tea at 3, or went to the gym at 4, then those would just as strongly be considered a social activity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is that a Cigarette or a Lollipop?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/is-that-a-cigarette-or-a-lollipop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/is-that-a-cigarette-or-a-lollipop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I saw a girl at a bus stop who appeared to have a cigarette in her mouth. &amp;ldquo;Yuck,&amp;rdquo; I thought. Then, I realized it was a lollipop. I immediately wanted to become her friend.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You see, there is something special about lollipops. As far as your mouth is concerned, you could just as well be eating a normal hard candy. But the stick makes a world’s difference. You are proclaiming to the world, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am enjoying a candy.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; There is no way to be inconspicuous about eating a lollipop. You have committed to this act, and do so with no shame.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gravity Summit Stanford: Wrap-up</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/gravity-summit-stanford-wrap-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2009 13:25:58 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/gravity-summit-stanford-wrap-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tuesday, May 5th was Gravity Summit&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Social Media Marketing for Business&amp;rdquo; at Stanford. I&amp;rsquo;ve known Rodney Rumford since Joachim and I made Graffiti for Facebook, and he was kind enough to save me a spot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The focus of the talks was very much aimed towards large businesses; presentations were given by such notable people as Bob Pearson of Dell, Inc. and Charles Miller from DIRECTV. That said, it seemed there were plenty of small business owners attending, and many of the points were generalizable. The main idea is:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a Better Writer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/becoming-a-better-writer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 15:39:05 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/becoming-a-better-writer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I just ordered Strunk &amp;amp; White&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Elements of Style,&amp;rdquo; 50th anniversary edition. I don&amp;rsquo;t have the book yet, but the purchase inspired me to pay more attention to writing. Hopefully this can be someplace where I can practice writing, incorporating new ideas and polishing my prose. No high hopes yet, as I don&amp;rsquo;t often continue such things for long, but we&amp;rsquo;ll see how it goes :)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dinner for 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/dinner-for-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 13:39:50 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/dinner-for-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was at a restaurant last night and saw a couple having dinner together. At a few points, the guy was texting on his phone and the girl was looking really bored. Boo on him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And then once he finished he left his phone sitting open on the table. I guess he was expecting replies? Maybe that sort of thing is commonplace now, but I still think it&amp;rsquo;s rude.  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Movie Watch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/upcoming-movie-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 04:49:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/upcoming-movie-watch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Documentary Type&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.apple.com/trailers/weinstein/whereintheworldisosamabinladen/trailer/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt; Where in the World is Osama Bin Laden?&lt;/a&gt; - Before you write this movie off as one that sounds like it was done by those guys that make stupid teen movies (I almost did), go watch the trailer. It&amp;rsquo;s done by the guy who made Supersize Me, and chronicles his quest to find Osama Bin Laden. And the trailer plays Gogol Bordello music.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.apple.com/trailers/independent/planetbboy/trailer/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Planet B-Boy&lt;/a&gt; - A documentary on the breakdancing culture. This movie looks awesome.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outside of Target</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/outside-of-target/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 17:46:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/outside-of-target/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The other day, a woman asked me if I could spare some change for poor women and children, and my automatic response was to keep walking with no response. Then, as I was walking away she called out to me and said &amp;ldquo;God bless you.&amp;rdquo; Hearing that made me feel like an awful person, because I certainly didn&amp;rsquo;t do anything to deserve it. It was on my mind for a while after that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political surveys</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/political-surveys/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 13:39:43 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/political-surveys/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Studies show that people become much more likely to vote if somebody calls them and asks, &amp;ldquo;Are you planning on voting?&amp;rdquo; which is why all of the people who try to promote a certain candidate always start off with that question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Could you also ask somebody &amp;ldquo;Are you planning on buying a new Apple computer within the next month?&amp;rdquo; to boost sales?  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why vote?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 09:05:16 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-vote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;People say that voting doesn&amp;rsquo;t really matter, because in the big picture, one vote for one candidate isn&amp;rsquo;t really going to make that much difference. And this is something that I&amp;rsquo;ve had a hard time coming to terms with too, but I think I figured it out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The point of voting is not to ensure that the right person gets elected or that the right ideas get placed in motion, because, as mentioned above, one vote is not really going to make a huge difference. Rather, &lt;i&gt;I think the point of voting is to be aware of the issues and to care about them to the point where you are able to publicly commit to what you believe.&lt;/i&gt; Once you have enough people caring about issues and participating in the argument, then you can finally start seeing great changes that save people, nations, and ideals. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
