<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/google/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 10:31:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/google/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Copy and paste across Google Slides</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/paste-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 10:31:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/paste-slides/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I wanted to copy slides from one Google Slide document to another. Half-expecting it to not work, I just copied slides in one document, switched to a different tab, hit paste&amp;hellip; and it worked! Seamless and perfect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It looks like when you copy slides, your clipboard actually saves a special payload that contains information about the slides you are copying, rather than the raw content. Then when you paste that into a Slides document, it retrieves the slide data from its servers and imports them to the second document. I imagine you have to be logged into the same Google account in both tabs for it to work properly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s AlphaZero Destroys Stockfish In 100-Game Match</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/google-s-alphazero-destroys-stockfish-in-100-game-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 22:58:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/google-s-alphazero-destroys-stockfish-in-100-game-match/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Google&amp;rsquo;s AlphaZero program is a machine that plays chess, and it has managed to quickly become the strongest chess AI in the world by implementing machine learning techniques. While existing chess AIs have mostly been massive dictionaries of moves that are put together by humans, AlphaZero learned chess entirely on its own with minimal human input.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I understand it, the hardest part of creating an AI that solves problems like chess is finding some way to calculate if you&amp;rsquo;re winning or not. If that were easy to do, the program could just look at all of its possible moves (which is not very many for a computer) and see which one would leave it winning by more. The trouble is that it&amp;rsquo;s very hard to tell if you&amp;rsquo;re winning. You might need to consider all possible outcomes many moves in advance, which quickly becomes too many to calculate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geoguessr</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/geoguessr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/geoguessr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;See a Google Street View at a random point in the world, guess where it is on a map.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterations of Google&#39;s logo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/iterations-of-googles-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 17:43:59 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/iterations-of-googles-logo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m definitely glad they keep iterating until they got to the current version, but that 2nd revision&amp;rsquo;s pretty neat too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
