<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pokemon on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/pokemon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pokemon on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2014 18:49:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/pokemon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Missingno. in Pokemon Fusion</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/missingno-in-pokemon-fusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2014 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/missingno-in-pokemon-fusion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve made a small update to the &lt;a href=&#34;http://pokemon.alexonsager.net&#34;&gt;Pokemon Fusion&lt;/a&gt; site, and added Missingno. as a hidden pokemon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was inspired by the incredible Mewtwo x Missingno. fusion artwork that was posted by StarvingStudents on his &lt;a href=&#34;http://starvingstudents.deviantart.com/art/Mewssingno-472862222&#34;&gt;deviantART page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Missingno. appears whenever there is an invalid ID in the URL, so acts as a fun 404 page. You can try it out &lt;a href=&#34;http://pokemon.alexonsager.net/25/0&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/assets/images/pikassingno.png&#34; alt=&#34;Pikassingno.&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The glich images were generated with ImageMagick (the Rmagick ruby gem in particular), using the spread function to displace pixels by a certain amount. In this case, I also shrunk the image first to exaggerate the pixelation, and it brought it back to normal size afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Fusion: Behind the Scenes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/behind-the-scenes-pokemon-fusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2013 00:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/behind-the-scenes-pokemon-fusion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting a few questions about the script used to generate the &lt;a href=&#34;http://pokemon.alexonsager.net&#34;&gt;Pokemon Fusion&lt;/a&gt; sprites, so I thought I would write a quick blog post to describe the process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The inspiration of the website was the idea that it should be possible to automate the process of combining pokemon sprites, and each image is automatically generated by a computer script. Some of the results are less impressive than others, but I think that it adds to the fun and makes it that much more satisfying when you come across ones that work really well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
