<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/book/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/extremely-loud-and-incredibly-close/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/extremely-loud-and-incredibly-close/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazingly imaginative&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the story of Oskar Schell, a young boy who is on a quest around New York City, attempting to solve a mystery left in the wake of his father’s death in the 9/11 attacks. The story is told in the form of narratives, letters, and journal entries from the perspective of three individuals, and their interwoven stories are revealed expertly in parallel. The book works as a scrapbook, with the reader discovering elements from the story appearing on the pages, as though they had been pasted in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Elegance of the Hedgehog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-elegance-of-the-hedgehog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-elegance-of-the-hedgehog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Profoundly moving&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By Muriel Barbery, this novel is the story of two hyper-intelligent individuals living among Paris’ high society: Renée Michel, the concierge of the apartment building, and Paloma Josse, the shockingly perceptive 12-year-old. They seem to embody everything that the privileged elite should be but isn’t; the juxtaposition of their wisdom and class against the frivolous and shallow natures of those around them constantly lashes out at the empty finicking of the bourgeois lifestyles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
