<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Health on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Health on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:25:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>/future</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:25:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/future/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Things I am looking forward to in&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-year-2026&#34;&gt;The year 2026&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;fridays&#34;&gt;Fridays&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kid2 will enter kindergarten, which means a sudden increase in time with no kids in the house. Since I work remotely on Fridays, this creates some opportunities for precious free-time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It will be really nice to be able to spend some quiet time during the day with my wife. I would love to have semi-regular lunch dates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The kids&amp;rsquo; swimming school has a plan that lets parents of enrolled kids use the pool freely for a very reasonable monthly fee. I want to start swimming on Friday mornings. I&amp;rsquo;m terrible at swimming, but I do want to get better, and I&amp;rsquo;m hopeful that it will be a good source of exercise.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Lighting in the Office</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/natural-lighting-in-the-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/natural-lighting-in-the-office/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve come to learn that I really enjoy working in environments with only natural lighting. At my job, I work in a large open room with about 50 people. Many of them are artists who need to minimize the glare on their screens, so the great big windows covering the walls of our room are always covered with blinds, and we instead have fluorescent lights turned on (these do cause glare too, but at least they are more predictable so people can tilt their screens to minimize it).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
