<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/social/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/social/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I want to love Mastodon...</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/i-want-to-love-mastodon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/i-want-to-love-mastodon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;But it&amp;rsquo;s just not doing it for me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[!NOTE] Update 2024/12/27&#xA;I have set up my own instance of GoToSocial, and have written about it [[installing-gotosocial-on-coolify | here]].&#xA;This seems like the best solution for me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The main selling point of Mastodon is its &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.joinmastodon.org/#federation&#34;&gt;federation&lt;/a&gt; I think, and I tend to agree with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tbray.org/ongoing/When/202x/2024/11/15/Not-Bluesky&#34;&gt;Tim Bray&amp;rsquo;s points&lt;/a&gt; that some kind of decentralized, protocol-based network for social exchange is what will endure. Having one service run by one group of people is brittle. Having many services run by many groups of people is resilient.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meals as a Social Activity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/meals-as-a-social-activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/meals-as-a-social-activity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I ate dinner alone. I think there is nothing wrong with that, but you just don’t see people alone in restaurants all that often (Aren’t you going to be bored? Do you want a magazine or something?). Eating meals, in most cultures everywhere, is regarded as a social activity. I would like to explore why, and have a few hypotheses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Everybody has to do it&lt;/strong&gt;. Three times a day, nearly everybody will eat food at roughly the same time. People share this activity, and so it makes sense for that time to be designated for social interaction. If everybody had tea at 3, or went to the gym at 4, then those would just as strongly be considered a social activity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
