<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Universal Basic Income</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/universal-basic-income/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/universal-basic-income/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I wonder sometimes about what a better society than ours would be. What should our goals be as we try to improve?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As our society improves and we get more efficient, I like to imagine a future where we don&amp;rsquo;t have to work as much. That seems like a nice thing to aim for. Universal basic income (UBI) seems like one possible solution. If we could afford to give everybody a fixed minimal income, people could work less and still have a basic amount of wealth needed to survive. But I&amp;rsquo;m not yet convinced whether UBI is the correct answer to describe an ideal future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Is No Longer a Communication Platform</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/facebook-is-no-longer-a-communication-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 19:53:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/facebook-is-no-longer-a-communication-platform/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I started using Facebook in 2005, it was exclusive to college students and was by far the best way to communicate with my classmates. It was the first time I could learn what my friends were up to without asking each one individually. Everything I wanted to know about my friends was in one easily accessible place.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All recent updates were shown as one long list, but Facebook eventually introduced the News Feed. This was an effort to filter everyone&amp;rsquo;s updates to show just the most important ones. Facebook made educated guesses about whose updates were most important to you and hid the ones you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t care about. I think they also kept an option to see all updates in chronological order if you didn&amp;rsquo;t want to miss out on anything.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perils of Eroded Civic Knowledge Forewarned by Former Justice Souter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/perils-of-eroded-civic-knowledge-forewarned-by-fmr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 18:43:32 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/perils-of-eroded-civic-knowledge-forewarned-by-fmr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is extremely important.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let’s stop the hate</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lets-stop-the-hate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 18:44:38 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lets-stop-the-hate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m a supporter of LGBT rights. I&#39;m generally not too vocal about it, but with recent events culminating in the Orlando mass shootings, I had to say something.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve been thinking a lot about the LGBT rights movement recently. Hopefully this effort can be another step forward following the Civil Rights Movement, as we work towards equal rights and treatment for all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Civil Rights Act made it illegal to discriminate based on race, color, religion, sex, or national origin. Setting religion aside for a moment, the rest are distinctions that generally lead to noticeable physical differences. The ease of identification is probably one factor that helped the prejudice spread so much, and led to institutional disenfranchisement as well as terrible acts of discrimination and violence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Internet With A Human Face</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/the-internet-with-a-human-face/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/the-internet-with-a-human-face/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An excellent talk by Maciej Cegłowski on the bleak state of mass surveillance the internet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco Is Dead. Long Live San Francisco</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/san-francisco-is-dead-long-live-san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/san-francisco-is-dead-long-live-san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.modernluxury.com/san-francisco/story/san-francisco-dead-long-live-san-francisco&#34;&gt;Gary Kamiya&lt;/a&gt; in San Francisco Magazine, talking about the many factors and consequences of San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(I)f present trends continue, the city could soon become a moated citadel of info-money, accessible only to venture capitalists, Twitter engineers, and the creators of hookup apps.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This prospect worries me. As someone who loves San Francisco’s maverick tradition and its class and ethnic diversity (I celebrated both in a book I wrote last year called Cool Gray City of Love), I find the idea that my beloved town is on the verge of becoming another Manhattan—a picturesque but increasingly expensive, homogeneous, and sterile burg—distressing, to put it mildly.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And yet, the political, cultural, and class war that has erupted over what is happening to San Francisco—call it the Change—strikes me as wrongheaded to the point of surreality.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I’m all for rushing the barricades when there’s an enemy to fight and a battle that can be won. I’ve engaged in my share of such battles. But it’s time to reckon with reality: There is no enemy here. Or if there is, it’s an enemy that won’t be defeated. What has hit San Francisco in the last couple of years can be summed up in one word: capitalism. And that is a tsunami that no seawall can keep out.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Gitmo is Killing Me&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/gitmo-is-killing-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 13:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/gitmo-is-killing-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A chilling story told by a prisoner at Guantanamo Bay. I hope that someday we&amp;rsquo;ll look back and wonder how anything like this could have been possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been detained at Guantánamo for 11 years and three months. I have never been charged with any crime. I have never received a trial.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The situation is desperate now. All of the detainees here are suffering deeply. At least 40 people here are on a hunger strike. People are fainting with exhaustion every day. I have vomited blood.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And there is no end in sight to our imprisonment. Denying ourselves food and risking death every day is the choice we have made.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I just hope that because of the pain we are suffering, the eyes of the world will once again look to Guantánamo before it is too late.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political surveys</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/political-surveys/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 13:39:43 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/political-surveys/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Studies show that people become much more likely to vote if somebody calls them and asks, &amp;ldquo;Are you planning on voting?&amp;rdquo; which is why all of the people who try to promote a certain candidate always start off with that question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Could you also ask somebody &amp;ldquo;Are you planning on buying a new Apple computer within the next month?&amp;rdquo; to boost sales?  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why vote?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 09:05:16 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-vote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;People say that voting doesn&amp;rsquo;t really matter, because in the big picture, one vote for one candidate isn&amp;rsquo;t really going to make that much difference. And this is something that I&amp;rsquo;ve had a hard time coming to terms with too, but I think I figured it out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The point of voting is not to ensure that the right person gets elected or that the right ideas get placed in motion, because, as mentioned above, one vote is not really going to make a huge difference. Rather, &lt;i&gt;I think the point of voting is to be aware of the issues and to care about them to the point where you are able to publicly commit to what you believe.&lt;/i&gt; Once you have enough people caring about issues and participating in the argument, then you can finally start seeing great changes that save people, nations, and ideals. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
