<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Idea on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/idea/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Idea on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/idea/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Music of the City - an Art Project Idea</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/music-of-the-city---an-art-project-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/music-of-the-city---an-art-project-idea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve had an idea for a fun art project in my head for many years now, and I don&amp;rsquo;t see myself going through with it any time soon, so I&amp;rsquo;ll compromise by just writing about it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The idea is to photograph people (with permission) who are wearing headphones in the city. Their photo will be shown along with the song they happened to be listening to. It would be interesting to see if a viewer would see any correlation between a person&amp;rsquo;s visual appearance and their taste in music. The prompt &amp;ldquo;What song was playing right now&amp;rdquo; is much more interesting than &amp;ldquo;What is your favorite music,&amp;rdquo; and some people might think that I caught them at just the wrong time, making things more fun for me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Idea: PvP Pac-Man</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pvp-pacman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pvp-pacman/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;concept&#34;&gt;Concept&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Play Pac-Man online against other players. 1 player plays as Pac-Man and 4 other players play as the ghosts. Pac-Man&amp;rsquo;s goal is to collect as many dots as possible, and the ghosts&amp;rsquo; goal is to work together to catch Pac-Man. Players receive points at the end of the round based on performance, and roles are rotated for the next round.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;gameplay&#34;&gt;Gameplay&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In terms of strategy, the ghosts will need to work together in order to win. Pac-Man will move faster than the ghosts, so the ghosts&amp;rsquo; main strategy will be to trap Pac-Man in a corner. To encourage teamwork, all ghosts will receive the same amount of points at the end of round regardless of who actually caught Pac-Man.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
