<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Review on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Desk mat</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/desk-mat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/desk-mat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;currently-using&#34;&gt;Currently using&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;30cm×85cm wool desk mat from &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.co.jp/dp/B0CRPZZBFS&#34;&gt;amesoba&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;amesoba-mat.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;My current desk setup&#34; title=&#34;My current desk setup&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This desk mat is fantastic. The natural wool material has been treated to have none of the typical scratchiness, and it&amp;rsquo;s comfortable for my wrists while giving a smooth surface for a mouse, too.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;30×90 is a more standard size, but 90cm felt a little bit too big for me, so this 85cm width is perfect.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rambling about — Keyboards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/r-keyboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:36:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/r-keyboards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I use an &lt;a href=&#34;https://iqunix.com/products/magi65&#34;&gt;IQUNIX Magi65&lt;/a&gt; keyboard at home, and absolutely love it. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get the Pro version, as I don&amp;rsquo;t really need a dial or media keys, and I preferred the smaller size anyways. The only real criticism I noticed in reviews was that the keyboard is pretty heavy, but this turned out to be a good thing for me. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to carry the thing around with me, and I love the solidity as I type. The typing experience is fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit: Become Human</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/detroit-become-human/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/detroit-become-human/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/2020/detroit.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;aside&#34;&gt;In this review, I&#39;ll talk about a few parts of the game that stood out to me, and I&#39;ll do my best to do so while avoiding spoilers.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Detroit: Become Human&lt;/em&gt; is a story-heavy adventure game developed by Quantic Dream, the studio I knew best as the creators of &lt;em&gt;Heavy Rain&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The story takes place in a future where androids are commonplace and indistinguishable from humans aside from a computer chip placed on their temple. Predictably, the androids are mistreated and repressed by humans, and you eventually find yourself in the middle of a robot uprising.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAVA Ora Unica Wristwatch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/nava-ora-unica-wristwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/nava-ora-unica-wristwatch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/ora-unica-watch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I happened upon this watch in the mall over the weekend and loved how unconventional it is. The inner end of the loop acts as the hour hand, and the outer end is the minute hand. The in-between part seems to move freely, so you have a watch face that looks pretty different each time you look at it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;d probably need to pause for a few seconds to decipher the time so it&amp;rsquo;s not exactly practical, but it would be a good conversation starter for sure.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Cut of the Dead (カメラを止めるな！）</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/one-cut-of-the-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/one-cut-of-the-dead/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://kametome.net/index.html&#34;&gt;One Cut of the Dead (カメラを止めるな！)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is a low budget Japanese zombie movie that became hugely popular here. I just watched it over the weekend and it was wonderful. The writing is very funny and very clever, and when it was over I found myself immediately wanting to watch it a second time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/One_Cut_of_the_Dead&#34;&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One Cut of the Dead was made for 3 million Japanese Yen (approximately $25,000 in US Dollars at the time) with a cast of unknown actors. It was made in eight days after director Shinichiro Ueda participated in workshops for actors and filmmakers at the Enbu Seminar drama school in Tokyo&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargekey Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chargekey-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2014 20:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chargekey-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently received a review unit of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hellonomad.com/products/chargekey-iphone5&#34;&gt;Chargekey&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s essentially a key-sized USB to Lightning cable that you will can have available on your keychain (They also make a Micro-USB version to fit your Android phone). I don&amp;rsquo;t do too much wandering around during the day, but I hadn&amp;rsquo;t bought a second cable for charging my phone while at work so I was more than happy to start making daily use of this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on &#34;Sourcecode&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/thoughts-on-sourcecode/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/thoughts-on-sourcecode/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve finally come to terms with the movie &lt;em&gt;Sourcecode&lt;/em&gt;. But at first, I hated it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The premise is that scientists have built a machine that can:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;extract remnants of memory from a person&amp;rsquo;s brain and&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;allow a 2nd person&amp;rsquo;s consciousness to then enter those memories and experience them firsthand.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They then use this machine to have someone enter the memory of a person present at a train bombing, so that he can find the culprit and stop the next crime.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrono Trigger Retrospective</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/chrono-trigger-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/chrono-trigger-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Chrono Trigger basically began as a jam session — a couple of star designers and a manga artist getting together to brainstorm and seeing what they might produce. No pressure. No cynicism.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[ . . . ]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, the best thing about Chrono Trigger is something that can’t quite be quantified in terms of mechanics, aesthetics, or plot. It’s impossible to play without getting the sense that that its designers really had a lot of fun in conceiving it (barring a stomach ulcer or two) and were wholly dedicated to making sure they got it right. Chrono Trigger is a labor of love effected by a group of very talented game designers, and their enthusiasm for the project permeates every aspect of the experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Cups of Tea</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/three-cups-of-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/three-cups-of-tea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Three Cups of Tea&lt;/em&gt; is the most inspiring book I have ever read.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is the true story following Greg Mortenson, a mountaineer who attempts to climb K2. On his way down, he stumbles into a tiny village in Pakistan and vows to return one day to build a school for the children there. He is successful, and is urged by others to continue building schools for underprivileged children across Pakistan. His story is remarkable, and the amount of impact he has managed to bring as one man with audacious goals is astounding.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gogol Bordello – Oakland 2009</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/gogol-bordello-oakland-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/gogol-bordello-oakland-2009/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently saw Gogol Bordello perform live for the second time. The first was a year (two years?) ago in San Francisco, and it was the wildest, most exhilarating event I have ever attended. Many concerts have &amp;ldquo;that one song,&amp;rdquo; that brings the entire audience together in a fever of enthusiasm to focus entirely on the music and the performance. Gogol Bordello managed to maintain this state for the entire 2 hour show. The rush of being in a huge crowd of people screaming in unison and immersed in the moment, led by the gods of gypsy punk, was indescribable. But enough about last year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/extremely-loud-and-incredibly-close/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/extremely-loud-and-incredibly-close/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazingly imaginative&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the story of Oskar Schell, a young boy who is on a quest around New York City, attempting to solve a mystery left in the wake of his father’s death in the 9/11 attacks. The story is told in the form of narratives, letters, and journal entries from the perspective of three individuals, and their interwoven stories are revealed expertly in parallel. The book works as a scrapbook, with the reader discovering elements from the story appearing on the pages, as though they had been pasted in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Elegance of the Hedgehog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-elegance-of-the-hedgehog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-elegance-of-the-hedgehog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Profoundly moving&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By Muriel Barbery, this novel is the story of two hyper-intelligent individuals living among Paris’ high society: Renée Michel, the concierge of the apartment building, and Paloma Josse, the shockingly perceptive 12-year-old. They seem to embody everything that the privileged elite should be but isn’t; the juxtaposition of their wisdom and class against the frivolous and shallow natures of those around them constantly lashes out at the empty finicking of the bourgeois lifestyles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
